八 年 后
两 个 月 后
蜘蛛侠终将归来
小小升级了一下 托尼·斯塔克
嗨 哈皮 只是问候一下 我下午两点四十五分放学
我已经准备好执行下一个任务了
对了 我是彼得
帕克
流体学 三点零一版
返校日来了 你们准备好了吗
《学术十项全能》 华盛顿特区
德尔马熟食杂货店
彩虹商店
如果不是你的车 请不要偷走 来自蜘蛛侠的忠告
遇到身份盗用了吗 我们保护你
必胜客 熟食杂货店
第二十一街站
奈德
《学术十项全能》
距离巴尔的摩90英里 距离华盛顿126英里
哈皮
全美学术十项全能大赛
进入数据集
《训练轮协议》 请输入斯塔克企业密钥标识符
全美学术十项全能大赛
三飞饰 神盾局总部的代号
呼叫失败
全美学术十项全能大赛
蛛网液
斯塔顿岛
我从纽约之行中活下来了
老虎队
返校日
通行证
温莎领结的打法
抓获秃鹰飞行人
蜘蛛侠 附录：抱歉弄坏了你的飞机
飓风过山车
返校日舞会
中城科技高中 我们精益求精
未知号码 到卫生间来
这是你的了 托尼·斯塔克
一切都回不到从前了
Things are never gonna be the same now.
我说 瞧瞧这幅画
I mean, look at this.
上面有外星人
You got aliens.
还有个绿色的大家伙 把大楼都夷为平地
You got big green guys tearing down buildings.
我小时候喜欢画牛仔和印第安人
When I was a kid, I used to draw cowboys and Indians.
其实都是美洲原住民 但无所谓了
Actually, it's Native American, but whatever.
是啊 不过话说回来
Yeah. Tell you what, though.
这幅画画得还不错 对吧
It ain't bad, is it?
是挺好的
No. Yeah.
这个孩子大有前途
Kid's got a future.
嗯 这个嘛...
Yeah, well...
我们拭目以待吧
We'll see, I guess.
嗨 别那样
No, hey!
你不能直接把那东西锯穿
You can't saw through that stuff.
那些混蛋外星人强悍得很
These alien bastards are tough.
我们得用他们的家伙
You gotta use the stuff they use.
- 看到没 就这样 - 好的
- See? All right. - All right.
嗨
Oh, hey!
你终于来了 这都下午了
Glad you could join us. Afternoon.
- 是啊 我的闹钟没响 - 好吧 又是闹钟
- Yeah. My alarm didn't go off. - Yeah, your alarm.
听着 按我说的那样 把装甲板堆起来
Look, just go stack that armor plating like I asked you.
这是一单大买卖
This is a huge deal for us.
大家请注意
Attention, please!
根据396B号行政命令
In accordance with Executive Order 396B...
所有战后清理工作 现在都属于我们的管辖范围
all post-battle cleanup operations are now under our jurisdiction.
谢谢你的服务 这里就交给我们吧
Thank you for your service. We'll take it from here.
你们是谁
Who the hell are you?
专业人士
Qualified personnel.
听着 我跟市政府签署了合同清理这些废墟 所以...
Look, I have a city contract to salvage all this, okay, with the city, so...
抱歉 图姆斯先生 但所有清理工作现在由我们接管
I apologize, Mr. Toomes, but all salvage operations are now under our jurisdiction.
请转交你们收集到的所有外星物体
Please turn over any and all exotic materials that you've collected...
不然我们会起诉你
or you will be prosecuted.
女士 我应该...
Ma'am, what am...
拜托了 别走 嗨 女士 先别走
Please. Come here. Hey, lady, come on.
听着...
Look...
这些卡车是我专门为本次清理工作买的
I bought trucks for this job.
我还又雇了一组人
I brought in a whole new crew.
这些人都还要养家糊口 我也有家要养
These guys have a family. I have a family.
我所有家当都押这上面了 我会把房子都赔掉的
I'm all in on this. I could lose my house.
抱歉 先生 我无能为力
I'm sorry, sir. There's nothing I can do.
也许下次不要自不量力
Maybe next time, don't overextend yourself.
你刚说什么
What'd you say?
没错
Yeah.
他说得对 我是自不量力
He's right. I overextended myself.
- 嗨 嗨 - 别那样
- Hey, hey, hey. - Don't do it.
都放下枪
Put them down.
如果你有任何不满 可以去找我的上级
If you have a grievance, you may take it up with my superiors.
你的上级又是哪路神仙
Your superiors. Who the hell are they?
一个由斯塔克企业和政府损害控制部门组成的联合公司
A joint venture between Stark Industries and the government the Department of Damage Control,
会负责外星人残骸和其他外星材料的收集工作
will oversee the collection and storage of alien and other exotic materials.
搞出这堆烂摊子的那帮混蛋们 现在却收钱负责清理
Now the assholes who made this mess are paid to clean it up.
是啊 都是暗箱操作
Yeah, it's all rigged.
专家估计大概有1500多吨的外星材料
Experts estimate there are over 1500 tons of exotic material...
散落在纽约州 新泽西州和宾夕法尼亚州地区
scattered throughout the tri-state area.
嗨 头儿
Hey, chief!
昨天清理的一包外星材料还在这儿呢 我们应该上交 对吗
We have another load from yesterday. We're supposed to turn this in, right?
我才不管
I ain't hauling it.
真是可惜
It's too bad.
我们本来可以从那堆外星垃圾里挑一些好东西出来
We could have made some cool stuff from all that alien junk.
这样吧
I tell you what.
我们留着吧
Let's keep it.
世道变了
The world's changing.
我们也该变一变了
It's time we change, too.
不赖嘛 梅森
There you go, Mason.
这桩生意有戏
Business is good.
纽约 皇后区
New York. Queens.
这地方虽然不怎么样 可这是家啊
It's a rough borough, but, hey, it's home.
你在跟谁说话
Who you talking to?
没人 就是沿途录些视频
No one. Just making a little video of the trip.
这东西不能给任何人看
You know you can't show it to anyone.
是 我知道
Yeah, I know.
那你为什么还要旁白
Then why are you narrating in that voice?
因为那样做很好玩啊
Because it's fun.
好玩
Fun.
他们为什么叫你"哈皮"
So why do they call you Happy?
赶紧下车 我不会帮你拎包的 我们走
Come on. I'm not carrying your bags. Let's go.
我能不能先去趟洗手间
Hey, should I go to the bathroom before?
里面有洗手间
There's a bathroom on it.
没有飞行员 太酷了
No pilot? That's awesome.
- 你要坐那儿 - 是的
- Is that where you're gonna sit? - Yeah.
你以前没坐过私人飞机
This is your first time on a private plane?
我什么飞机都没坐过
My first time on any plane.
它应不应该... 这种声音正常吗
Should it...? Should it be...? Should it be making that noise?
没人跟我说过我为什么要来柏林 或者我到底要做什么
No one has actually told me why I'm in Berlin or what I'm doing.
跟美国队长疯了有关
Something about Captain America going crazy.
你住这间
This is you.
我们的房间挨着吗
Oh, we're neighbors?
我们不是室友 赶紧把该穿的穿好
We're not roommates. Suit up.
好的 彼得 你搞得定的
Okay, Peter, you got this.
你穿的是什么啊
What the hell are you wearing?
我的战衣啊
It's my suit.
行李箱呢
Where's the case?
什么行李箱
What case?
什么 我还以为那是个壁橱
What? I thought that was a closet.
- 这里也是我房间 - 进去
- This is still my room? - Go, please.
- 我的房间好大... - 那边
- My room is way bigger than... - There.
我找到行李箱了 找到了
I found the case. I found the case.
"小小升级了一下"
"A minor upgrade"?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
- 穿上吧 - 怎么...
- Put it on. - What the...?
这是我见过的最酷的装备
This is the coolest thing I've ever seen...
- 我们走 - 可是 我还是不明白
- Let's go. - But, yeah. Well, I don't understand.
是为我准备的吗 哈皮 哈皮 你先别走
Is it for me? Happy. Happy, wait.
这也太酷了 太酷了
This is insane. Insane.
看看这身战衣 看啊 看看这双眼睛
Look at this thing. Look. Look at the eyes.
这是我这辈子最快乐的一天
This is the greatest day of my life.
- 我们走 - 好的
- Let's go. - Okay.
好的 美国队长 钢铁侠 黑寡妇都在那边
Okay, there's Captain America, Iron Man, Black Widow.
那个新来的人是谁
Who's that new guy?
- 睡衣宝宝 - 叫我呢 我得走了
- Underoos! - Oh, that's me. I gotta go. I gotta go.
大家好
Hey, everyone.
刚刚发生了超级不可思议的事
The craziest thing just happened.
我跟美国队长打了一架 我偷了他的盾 然后朝他砸去
I just had a fight with Captain America. I stole his shield. I threw it at him...
怎么回事 他变这么大了 我得走了 稍等片刻
What the hell? He's big now. I gotta go. Hang on.
简直不要太赞 斯塔克先生说 "嗨 新来的"
It was the most amazing thing! Mr. Stark was like, "Hey, Underoos!"
我一个空翻过去 偷了队长的盾牌 我跟所有人打招呼 "大家好啊"
I flipped in and stole Cap's shield. I was like, "What's up, everybody?"
然后... 嗨 稍等一下
And then... Hey, just a second!
马上就来
Coming!
嗨
Hey.
这墙隔音效果不太好
We have thin walls here.
你在干嘛 拍视频日记
What are you doing, a little video diary?
- 是啊 - 没关系
- Yeah. - It's all right.
- 我也会这么做 - 我跟他说过不能这样
- I'd do the same thing. - I told him not to.
- 他一直在拍 我会把内容都删掉的 - 好吧
- He was filming. I'm gonna wipe the chip. - Okay.
嗨 这样吧
Hey. You know what?
我们应该给梅婶录制一个你的不在场视频 准备好了吗
We should make an alibi video for your aunt anyway. You ready?
- 不在场证明 没问题 - 开拍了吗 进到镜头里来
- An alibi? Sure. Okay. - We rolling? Get in the frame.
嗨 梅 近来如何 你穿着什么 希望是清凉一点的
Hey, May. How you doing? What are you wearing? Something skimpy, I hope.
彼得 我刚才那话太没礼貌了 我们重新拍 你到时候可以剪辑一下
Peter, that's inappropriate. Let's start over. You can edit it.
一 二 三 嗨 梅
Three, two, one. Hey, May.
我的天 你都不知道你侄子这周末
My gosh, I wanted to tell you what an incredible job your nephew did...
在斯塔克实习生操练中表现有多好
this weekend at the Stark internship retreat.
另所有人都刮目相看
Everyone was impressed.
真是够了 有车并线 不好意思
Come on! It's a freaking merge. I'm sorry.
因为你不是在皇后大道上
This is because you're not on Queens Boulevard.
看到没 哈皮希望去做资产管理
See, Happy is hoping to get bumped up to asset management.
他之前是安全部门的主管 再之前是个司机
He was forehead of security, before that he was a driver.
这话请你私下再讲
That was a private conversation.
我不喜欢别人拿这事开玩笑 我也不想谈这事
I don't like joking about this. It was hard to talk about that.
- 不 说真的 他是不是总打呼噜 - 好了 我们到了
- No, seriously, was he snoring a bunch? - Here we are. End of the line.
- 哈皮 可以回避一下吗 - 你让我走开
- Can you give us a moment? - Want me to leave?
把彼得的箱子从后备箱拿出来
Grab Peter's case out of the trunk.
我能留着这套战衣
I can keep the suit?
可以 我们刚才说过了
Yes, we were just talking about it.
但请帮我个忙 哈皮是你的联络人
Do me a favor, though. Happy's kind of your point guy on this.
别总是惹毛他 别做蠢事
Don't stress him out. Don't do anything stupid.
我看过他的心电图
I've seen his cardiogram.
- 行吗 - 行
- All right? - Yes.
我做什么你都不要跟着做 也不要做我不会做的事
Don't do anything I would do, and don't do anything I wouldn't do.
两条界限之间有一小条灰色地带 这就是你的行事范围
There's a little gray area in there. That's where you operate.
- 等下 这意味着我是位复仇者 - 不
- Wait, does that mean I'm an Avenger? - No.
- 是这个吗 - 送上七楼
- This it? - Seventh floor.
- 我可以自己拿上去 不用劳烦你 - 你自己拿上去
- I can take that. You don't have to. - You'll take it?
- 嗯 我拿上去就好 - 谢谢
- Yeah, I can take that. - Thank you.
那我们下次"练手"是什么时候 你知道吗
So when's our next...? When's our next "retreat," you know?
你是说下次任务
What, next mission?
没错 我说的就是任务
Yeah, the mission. The missions.
我们会打给你
We'll call you.
你有我电话吗
Do you have my numbers?
不 我刚说的是"我们"会打给你
No, I mean, we'll call you.
有人会打给你的 行吗
Like, someone will call you. All right?
- 你们队里的人 - 好的 就这样吧
- From your team. - Okay. All right.
我不是想抱你 开车门而已 咱俩关系还没到那地步
It's not a hug. I'm just grabbing the door for you. We're not there yet.
回见
Bye.
他们会打给我的
They're gonna call me.
你好啊 "屁"得·帕克
What's up, Penis Parker?
欢迎大家收看《中城科技》
Rise and shine, Midtown Science and Technology.
别忘了带你们的返校日门票
Don't forget about your homecoming tickets.
你有返校日派对的男伴了吗
Do you have a date for homecoming?
谢了 詹森 但我已经有男伴了
Thanks, Jason, but I already have a date.
- 好吧 - 嗯
- Okay. - Yeah.
该死 你现在就去我办公室
Damn it. You, in my office right now.
加入我 跟我一起建立新的乐高死星
Join me, and together we'll build my new LEGO Death Star.
- 你说什么 - 真无趣
- What? - So lame.
太棒了 一共多少块
That's awesome. How many pieces?
三千八百零三块
Three thousand eight hundred and three.
- 太酷了 - 当然 你今晚想拼吗
- That's insane. - I know. You want to build it tonight?
不行 今晚不行 我还要去斯塔克...
No, I can't tonight. I've got the Stark...
- 斯塔克实习项目 - 对的 没错
- Stark internship. - Yeah, exactly.
总是为那个项目跑来跑去
Always got that internship.
希望最后能成功转正
Yeah, well, hopefully, soon it'll lead to a real job with them.
- 那样的话就太美妙了 - 是吧
- That would be so sweet. - Right?
大家都会说 "那些工作表做得真好 彼得
He'd be all, "Good job on those spreadsheets, Peter.
给你一枚金币做奖励"
Here's a gold coin."
我不知道真正的工作是怎样的
I don't know how jobs work.
他们就是这样工作的
That's exactly how they work.
我会先把死星的架构搭起来
I'll knock out the bones of the Death Star.
其他部分就好办了 因为底座最不好搭
I'll come by afterwards. For the most part, the difficult thing is the base of it.
上面那一部分我们最多两个小时就能搭建好
The top half we can knock out in two hours, tops.
那就太好了
That'd be great.
我要迟到了
I'm gonna be late.
好的 那我们如何计算A点和B点之间的距离
Okay, so how do we calculate linear acceleration between points A and B?
弗拉什
Flash.
质量除以正弦函数和重力
It's the product of sine of the angle and gravity divided by mass.
不对 彼得 你在听吗
Nope. Peter. You still with us?
在听 在听
Yeah, yeah.
质量被抵消 所以只需考虑重力倍数正弦
Mass cancels out, so it's just gravity times sine.
正确 看到没 弗拉什 答得快不一定答得对
Right. See, Flash, being the fastest isn't always the best if you are wrong.
你死定了
You're dead.
今天我们要说说丹麦物理学家 尼尔斯·玻尔
Today we're talking about Danish physicist Niels Bohr...
但相信我 玻尔有关量子学的理论一点都不枯燥
but trust me, there's nothing Bohr-ing about his discoveries regarding quantum theory.
莉兹穿的那件上衣是不是新的
Did Liz get a new top?
不 之前见她穿过 但那条超短裙没见过
No. We've seen that before, but never with that skirt.
- 莉兹 嗨 标语真漂亮 - 嗨
- Liz, hey. That looks so good. - Hi!
我们不能再盯着人家看了 不然太过诡异
We should probably stop staring before it gets creepy.
太迟了
Too late.
你们两个就是屌丝
You guys are losers.
那你为什么还要跟我们坐一起
Well, then why do you sit with us?
因为我没朋友
Because I don't have any friends.
下一个问题
Next question.
最重的自然元素是什么
What is the heaviest naturally-occurring element?
氢质量最轻
Hydrogen's the lightest.
问题不是这个 好吧
That's not the question. Okay.
- 好的 - 铀
- Yeah. - Uranium.
答对了 谢谢你 亚伯拉罕
Correct. Thank you, Abraham.
请将书本翻至第十页
Please open your books to page 10.
彼得 这可是全国竞赛啊
Peter, it's nationals.
你就不能休一个周末
Is there no way you could take one weekend off?
我去不了华盛顿 如果斯塔克先生需要我 我一定得过去
I can't go to Washington. If Mr. Stark needs me, I have to make sure I'm here.
你都没见过托尼·斯塔克
You've never been in the same room as Tony Stark.
等下 怎么了
Wait. What's happening?
- 彼得不能去华盛顿 - 不行
- Peter's not going to Washington. - No.
- 绝对不行 - 为什么不行
- No, no, no. - Why not?
真的吗 马上就要全国赛了
Really? Right before nationals?
他已经退出了军乐队和机器人实验室
He already quit marching band and robotics lab.
我没有迷恋他 不过善于观察罢了
I'm not obsessed with him. Just very observant.
弗拉什 那你替彼得去吧
Flash, you're in for Peter.
不好说 我得先看看自己的安排
I don't know. I gotta check my calendar first.
我还要跟黑寡妇约会呢
I got a hot date with Black Widow coming up.
纯粹瞎编
That is false.
又拿那个铃来搞笑 我之前是怎么跟你说的
What'd I tell you about using the bell for comedic purposes?
- 嗨 你好 - 嗨 伙计
- Hey, what's up? - Hey, man.
你好 德尔马先生
What's up, Mr. Delmar?
嗨 帕克先生
Hey, Mr. Parker.
还要五号套餐 对吗
Number five, right?
没错 还有腌黄瓜 你能把黄瓜压平吗 谢谢
Yeah, and with pickles, and can you smush it down real flat? Thanks.
知道了 老板
You got it, boss.
你婶婶怎么样
How's your aunt?
她挺好的
Yeah, she's all right.
她是个非常性感的意大利女人
She's a very hot Italian woman.
你女儿怎么样
How's your daughter?
- 十美元 - 明明是五美元
- Ten dollars. - It's 5 dollars.
让你嘴贱 十美元
For that comment, 10 dollars.
嗨 不是吧 我开个玩笑而已
Hey, come on. I'm joking. I'm joking.
给你五美元
Here's 5 dollars.
你好 默夫
What's up, Murph?
近来如何 小家伙
How you doing, buddy?
学校那边如何
So how's school?
无聊 不过我有更有意思的事情去做
It's boring. Got better things to do.
好好读书 孩子 不然你最后会落得我这样的下场
Stay in school, kid. Otherwise, you're gonna end up like me.
- 有家店也蛮好的 - 皇后区最好吃的三明治
- This is great. - Best sandwiches in Queens.
真不容易
Finally.
你有病啊
What's the matter with you?
能帮我拿一下吗
Could you hold this?
谢了
Thanks.
嗨 这是谁的自行车 没人要
Hey, is this anybody's bike? No?
- 嗨 兄弟 这车是你的吗 - 我没零钱
- Hey, buddy, is this your bike? - I have no change.
谁有笔 你有笔吗
Does anyone have a pen? Do you have a pen?
大家都挺好的吧
Everybody good?
嗨
Hey!
你就是油管上那个蜘蛛人吗
You're that spider guy on YouTube, right?
请叫我蜘蛛侠
Call me Spider-Man.
好的 蜘蛛侠 翻个跟头给我看看
Okay, Spider-Man. Do a flip.
- 太棒了 - 还不错
- Yeah! - Not bad.
嗨 兄弟
Hey, buddy.
- 你不该偷车的 这样不好 - 这是我的车 蠢货
- Shouldn't steal cars, it's bad. - It's my car, dumbass!
嗨 让你的车别乱叫
Hey! Shut that off!
- 你能不能告诉他这车是我的 - 我正...
- Can you tell him it's my car? - I was...
- 我上夜班 拜托 - 那不是你的车
- I work at nights. Come on. - That's not your car!
- 那是他的车 - 我怎么知道
- That's his car. - How was I supposed to know?
- 他把那东西放在玻璃上 - 每天车都乱响 吵死了
- He was putting that in the window! - Every day with these alarms!
- 别再让车响了 - 别逼我下去 小流氓
- Turn it off! - Don't make me come down there, punk.
嗨 盖瑞 近来如何
Hey, Gary. How you doing?
马乔里 你好 你妈妈怎么样了
Marjorie, how are you? How's your mother?
我没事 没事
I'm good, I'm good.
您已经被转接至
You have reached the voicemail box of:
哈皮·霍根的语音信箱
Happy Hogan.
嗨 哈皮 我向你汇报今晚的行动
Hey, Happy. Here's my report for tonight.
我阻止了一件自行车盗窃大案
I stopped a grand theft bicycle.
找不到车主 所以留了张字条
Couldn't find the owner, so I just left a note.
我帮了一位迷路的多明尼加老奶奶
I helped this lost, old Dominican lady.
她人超好 还给我买了根西班牙油条
She was really nice and bought me a churro.
我觉得自己还能派上更大用场
I just feel like I could be doing more.
我很想知道下次的真实任务是什么
You know? Just curious when the next real mission's gonna be.
记得回我电话
So, yeah, just call me back.
我是彼得 彼得·帕克
It's Peter. Parker.
我干嘛要跟他说西班牙油条的事
Why would I tell him about the churro?
嗨
Hey, hey.
好的
Okay.
我已经等不及了
Can't wait to see this thing.
我终于可以大展拳脚了
Finally, something good.
高科技就是省事儿啊
Yo, this high-tech stuff makes it too easy.
- 我都跟你说了 买了绝对不会吃亏 - 快闪开
- Told you it was worth it. - Okay, go, go, go.
太牛了
Oh, nice.
今晚我们至少还能去五个地方蹲点
We can hit, like, five more places tonight.
你们好啊 伙计们 忘记取款密码了
What's up, guys? You forget your PIN number?
你们是复仇者联盟啊
You're the Avengers.
你们在这里干嘛
What are you guys doing here?
雷神 绿巨人 终于见到你们了
Thor. Hulk. Good to finally meet you guys.
我还以为你本人更帅呢
I thought you'd be more handsome in person.
钢铁侠
Iron Man.
你干嘛抢银行啊 你明明就是亿万富翁啊
Hey, what are you doing robbing a bank? You're a billionaire.
嗨
Hey...
感觉好奇怪
Oh, this feels so weird.
那是什么东西
What is that thing?
我开始觉得 你们不是复仇者联盟的人了
I'm starting to think you're not the Avengers.
911热线 您有什么紧急情况
911. What's your emergency?
蜘蛛侠跟复仇者在二十一大街一家银行里打起来了
Spider-Man is fighting the Avengers in a bank on 21st Street.
行了 伙计们 就到这儿吧 我明天还上课呢
Let's wrap this up. It's a school night.
你们这群蠢货怎么能有这么高科技的玩意儿
So how do jerks like you get tech like this?
不 等下 等下
No. Wait, wait, wait!
德尔马先生
Mr. Delmar.
德尔马先生 你在里面吗 这里有人吗
Hey, Mr. Delmar, you in here? Is anybody in here? Hello?
不是吧
Oh, come on.
我得...
I gotta...
- 给你 - 好的
- Here, here. - Good, yeah.
很好 就这样
Okay. Good. Yes.
对... 不 不 赶紧放下
Yes... No. No, put that down.
这玩意儿比你我都金贵 喂
That's worth more than you or me. Yeah?
哈皮 我刚遇到了一件超级奇怪的事 一伙抢自动取款机的人...
The craziest thing just happened. These guys were robbing an ATM...
- 携带有高科技武器... - 深呼吸 我没时间...
- with high-tech weapons... - Take a breath. I don't have time...
- 处理自动取款机抢劫案... - 我知道 可是...
- for ATM robberies... - Yeah, but...
或者你给我留的贴心留言 我正忙着搬家
or the notes you leave. I have moving day to worry about.
下周前一定得腾出地儿来
Everything's gotta be out next week.
- 等下 你要搬家吗 谁要搬家 - 是啊 你没看新闻吗
- Wait. You're moving? Who's moving? - Yeah, don't you watch the news?
托尼把复仇者大厦卖出去了 我们要搬去北部一个地方
Tony sold Avengers Tower. We're relocating to a new facility upstate...
- 但愿那里手机信号更差 - 那我怎么办
- where hopefully cell service is worse. - But what about me?
你怎么了
What about you?
万一斯塔克先生需要我 或者有什么要紧事呢
Well, what if Mr. Stark needs me or something big goes down?
- 我能跟斯塔克先生聊聊吗 - 远离过于危险事物就好
- Can I please talk to Mr. Stark? - Stay away from anything dangerous.
我必须要保证你负起责任来 懂吗
I'm responsible for making sure you're responsible, okay?
我做事当然负责 我... 糟了
I am responsible. I... Oh, crap.
- 我的背包不见了 - 这听起来可不像很负责的样子
- My backpack's gone. - That doesn't sound responsible.
- 我回头再打给你 - 还是别了
- I'll call you back. - Feel free not to.
怎么回事
What was that?
没什么 没什么
It's nothing. Nothing.
你就是蜘蛛侠
You're the Spider-Man.
- 油管上的蜘蛛侠 - 我不是
- From YouTube. - I'm not. I'm not.
- 你刚在房顶上 - 不是的 你在我房间里干嘛
- You were on the ceiling. - No. What are you doing in my room?
梅让我进来的 我们说好要一起搭好死星的
May let me in. We were gonna finish the Death Star.
那你也不能随便进我房间
You can't just bust into my room!
那个火鸡肉饼食谱一点都不靠谱
That turkey meatloaf recipe is a disaster.
我们吃晚饭吧 泰国菜如何 奈德 你爱吃泰国菜吗
Let's go to dinner. Thai? Ned, you want Thai?
- 爱 - 不 他有事
- Yes. - No. He's got a thing.
饭后才有事
A thing to do after.
好的
Okay.
穿件衣服吧
Maybe put on some clothes.
- 她不知道吗 - 没人知道
- Oh, she doesn't know? - Nobody knows.
斯塔克先生知道 因为我这身战衣是他做的 就这样
Mr. Stark knows because he made my suit. That's it.
托尼·斯塔克给你做的 你是复仇者联盟里的吗
Tony Stark made you that? Are you an Avenger?
差不多吧
Yeah, basically.
这事儿你得保密 不能告诉其他人
You can't tell anybody about this. You gotta keep it a secret.
- 保密 为什么 - 你知道她的脾气
- Secret? Why? - You know what she's like.
如果让她知道每晚有人追着杀我 她一定不会同意让我继续的
If she finds out people try and kill me every night, she won't let me do this.
拜托 奈德 求你了
Come on, Ned, please.
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay, okay.
跟你说实话吧 我不觉得我能保守住这个秘密
I'll level with you. I can't keep this a secret.
这明明是很酷的事情嘛
It's the greatest thing that's ever happened to me.
奈德 不能让梅知道 我现在不能这么对她
Ned, May cannot know. I cannot do that to her right now.
她经历了那么多事 我... 拜托了
You know? I mean, everything that's happened with her, I... Please.
- 好的 - 你能发誓吗
- Okay. - Just swear it, okay?
我发誓
I swear.
- 谢谢你 - 没关系
- Thank you. - Yeah.
居然被人发现了
I can't believe this is happening now.
- 我能试试你的战衣吗 - 不行
- Can I try the suit on? - No.
衣服上那些装置怎么用 有磁铁吗 你怎么发射粘液
How's it work? Magnets? How do you shoot the strings?
- 明天到学校了我再告诉你 - 太好了
- I'm gonna tell you at school tomorrow. - Great.
好 先等等
Okay, well, wait, then.
你又做蜘蛛侠 又参加斯塔克实习项目 是怎么做到的
How do you do this and the Stark internship?
这就是斯塔克实习项目
This is the Stark internship.
赶紧走吧
Just get out of here.
你是怎么回事
What's the matter?
我还以为你喜欢吃碎肉沙拉
Thought you loved larb.
太碎了吗 那就是不够碎了
It's too larby? Not larby enough.
我要说多少次"碎肉沙拉" 你才肯跟我说话
How many times do I have to say "larb" before you talk to me?
你知道我爱你
You know I larb you.
我就是压力太大 那个实习生项目搞得我很累
I'm just stressed. The internship, and I'm tired.
工作量太大
A lot of work.
斯塔克实习项目
The Stark internship.
老实说 我不喜欢托尼·斯塔克
I have to tell you, not a fan of that Tony Stark.
你总是一副心不在焉的样子 他肯定给你洗脑了
You're distracted all the time. He's got you in your head.
- 德尔马三明治店毁于... - 他究竟让你在做什么
- Delmar's Sandwiches was destroyed... - What does he have you doing?
- 一场爆炸... - 你得跟着直觉走
- in an explosion... - You need to use your instincts.
皇后区的犯罪被一名从天而降的犯罪阻挡者阻止了
after an ATM robbery was thwarted by Queens' own crime stopper...
怎么了
What?
蜘蛛侠
the Spider-Man.
蜘蛛侠努力阻止劫匪时
As the Spider-Man attempted to foil their heist...
银行突然发生剧烈爆炸 路对面的熟食杂货店被炸得粉碎
a powerful blast was set off, slicing through the bodega across the street.
神奇的是 爆炸并没有造成人员伤亡
Miraculously, no one was harmed.
如果你遇到了那种事 一定要转身向反方向跑
If you spot something like that happening, you turn and you run the other way.
知道 知道 当然
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Of course.
离我们就六个街区
Six blocks away from us.
我需要一个新背包
I need a new backpack.
- 你说什么 - 我需要一个新背包
- What? - I need a new backpack.
已经是第五个了
That's five.
- 糯米布丁 - 我们没点这个
- Sticky rice pudding. - We didn't order that.
店家免费赠送的 谢了
It's on the house. Thanks.
他人真好
That's nice of him.
我觉得他对你有意思
I think he larbs you.
你被蜘蛛咬了
You got bit by a spider?
它能咬我吗
Can it bite me?
不疼的 对吧
Well, it probably would've hurt, right?
管他呢 就算疼 我也会让它咬我
Whatever. Even if it did hurt, I'd let it bite me.
也许吧 有多疼
Maybe. How much did it hurt?
蜘蛛已经死了 奈德
The spider's dead, Ned.
爆炸时你在这儿
You were here?
没错
Yeah.
你可能没命的
You could've died.
那你产卵吗
Do you lay eggs?
你说什么 当然不会
What? No.
- 那你能吐毒液吗 - 不能
- Can you spit venom? - No.
你能召唤蜘蛛军团吗
Can you summon an army of spiders?
不能 奈德
No, Ned.
《索科维亚协议》签订于...
The Sokovia Accords were put into place....
你的粘液能发射多远
How far can you shoot your webs?
我不知道 闭嘴
It's unknown. Shut up.
开始调节...
to begin regulating....
我要是你 会站在楼顶上
If I was you, I would stand on a building...
- 尽力往远处发射... - 闭嘴 奈德
- and just shoot it as far as I could... - Shut up, Ned.
你好 我是美国队长 不论你是在教室还是在战场...
Hi. I'm Captain America. Whether you're in the classroom or on the battlefield...
- 你也认识他吗 - 嗯 我们见过
- Do you know him too? - Yeah, we met.
健康是决定成功与否的关键因素
fitness can be the difference between success or failure.
- 我偷过他的盾牌 - 什么
- I stole his shield. - What?
今天 我的好朋友 也就是你们的体育老师
Today, my good friend, your gym teacher...
将要发起美国队长健身挑战赛
will conduct the Captain America Fitness Challenge.
谢谢你 队长
Thank you, Captain.
虽然他是个不折不扣的战犯 我还是得播放这个视频
Pretty sure he's a war criminal, but I have to show these videos.
这是州政府规定的 开始吧
It's required by the state. Let's do it.
复仇者们需要纳税吗
Do Avengers have to pay taxes?
绿巨人闻起来什么味道
What does Hulk smell like?
- 他一定很好闻 - 赶紧闭嘴
- I bet he smells nice. - You have to shut up.
美国队长这人酷吗 或他是个尖酸刻薄的老头子
Is Captain America cool, or is he like a mean, old grandpa?
奈德 闭嘴 行吗
Ned, just... okay?
- 嗨 我能当你们的后勤人员吗 - 你说什么
- Hey, can I be your guy in the chair? - What?
总得需要个人带着耳机
Yeah. You know how there's a guy with a headset...
告诉其他人去哪儿吧
telling the other guy where to go?
如果你在一个着火的大楼里 我可以告诉你怎么逃出去
If you're in a burning building, I could tell you where to go.
我四周全是屏幕 我工作时就会在转椅上转来转去
There'd be screens around me, and I could swivel around.
- 我可以当你们的技术特工 - 我不需要技术特工
- I could be your guy in the chair. - I don't need a guy in the chair.
不错 帕克
Looking good, Parker.
我想上雷神 嫁给钢铁侠 然后杀死绿巨人
Now, see, for me, it would be F Thor, marry Iron Man and kill Hulk.
那蜘蛛侠呢
Well, what about the Spider-Man?
蜘蛛侠就是蜘蛛侠
It's just Spider-Man.
你们看油管上的银行安全录像了吗 他打跑了四个坏人
Did you see the bank security cam on YouTube? He fought off four guys.
天呐 她喜欢蜘蛛侠
Oh, my God, she's crushing on Spider-Man.
不会吧
No way.
- 算是吧 - 咦 好恶心哦
- Kind of. - Oh, gross.
- 他差不多都30了 - 你都不知道他长什么样子
- He's probably 30. - You don't know what he looks like.
万一他被严重烧伤了呢
Like, what if he's seriously burned?
我不在乎 我爱的是他的品性
I wouldn't care. I'd love him for the person he is inside.
彼得认识蜘蛛侠
Peter knows Spider-Man.
不 我不认识 不 我是说...
No, I don't. No. I... I mean...
他们是朋友
They're friends.
威尔逊教练和美国队长还是"朋友"呢
Yeah, like Coach Wilson and Captain America are friends.
我见过他 没错 见过几次
I've met him, yeah. A couple times.
不过是...
But it's...
通过斯塔克实习项目见到的
through the Stark internship.
对 我确实不该宣扬此事的
Yeah, well, I'm not really supposed to talk about it.
太棒了 这样吧
Well, that's awesome. Hey, you know what?
或许你可以邀请他参加莉兹的派对 好吗
Maybe you should invite him to Liz's party. Right?
好啊 我今晚有个派对 你要是能来就太好了
Yeah, I'm having people over tonight. You're more than welcome to come.
- 派对 - 没错 肯定会很劲爆的
- Having a party? - Yeah, it's gonna be dope.
你真该请你朋友蜘蛛侠过来
You should totally invite your personal friend Spider-Man.
没关系的
It's okay.
我理解彼得太忙 没时间参加派对 所以...
I know Peter's way too busy for parties anyway, so....
得了吧 他会去的 对吗 帕克
Come on. He'll be there. Right, Parker?
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
帮你啊
Helping you out.
你没听到她的话吗
Did you not hear her?
莉兹喜欢你
Liz has a crush on you.
伙计 你可是复仇者联盟的
Dude, you're an Avenger.
如果真有人能约到高年级的姑娘 肯定非你莫属了
If any one of us has a chance with a senior girl, it's you.
郊区家庭派对
House party in the suburbs.
我还记得这种场景 我有点嫉妒你呢
Oh, I remember these. Kind of jealous.
这会是永生难忘的一夜
It'll be a night to remember.
奈德 有的帽子很挑人的 你戴这顶简直太帅了
Ned, some hats wear men. You wear that hat.
是啊 这帽子让我自信满满
Yeah, it gives me confidence.
我们不该来
This is a mistake.
我们回家吧
Hey, let's just go home.
不是吧 彼得
Oh, Peter.
我理解 你正值青春期
I know. I know it's really hard...
想要融入大伙儿真的很难
trying to fit in with all the changes your body's going through.
你现在可正值花季
It's flowering now.
他最近压力好大
He's so stressed out lately.
派对有助于缓解压力
What helps with stress is a party.
- 我们应该去派对 - 行 我们去吧 我这就去
- We should go to the party. - Yeah, let's do it. I'm gonna go.
彼得
Peter.
- 好好玩儿 知道了吗 - 会的
- Have fun, okay? - I will.
拜 梅
Bye, May.
伙计 你带那身战衣了 对吧
Dude, you have the suit, right?
- 穿了 - 今晚会改变我们的一生
- Yeah. - This is gonna change our lives.
- 安妮 这边 - 嗨
- Annie, over here! - Hey.
嗨
Hey.
DJ弗拉什
DJ Flash.
这样 一会儿你变成蜘蛛侠飞进来
Okay. We're gonna have Spider-Man swing in...
夸赞所有人都很酷 跟我顶下拳 或者给我一个兄弟般的拥抱
say you guys are tight, and I get a fist bump or one of those half bro-hugs.
你们居然会参加这种无聊的派对
Can't believe you're at this lame party.
你不也在这儿嘛
But you're here too.
是吗
Am I?
天呐
Oh, my gosh.
嗨 你们好 奈德 帽子不错
Hey, guys. Cool hat, Ned.
- 嗨 莉兹 - 嗨 莉兹
- Hi, Liz. - Hi, Liz.
你们能来 我真是太开心了
I'm so happy you guys came.
家里有披萨和饮料 你们随意
There's pizza and drinks. Help yourself.
- 派对真赞 - 谢了
- What a great party. - Thanks.
我得...
Oh, I...
要是有东西被打碎了 我爸妈不会饶了我的 我得...
My parents will kill me if anything's broken. I gotta...
- 没关系 - 玩得开心
- Yeah. - Have fun.
- 拜 - 拜
- Bye. - Bye.
兄弟 你怎么想的
Dude, what are you doing?
她在这儿 赶紧变身蜘蛛人啊
She's here. Spider it up.
不 不行 我不能...不能这么做
No, no, no. I can't... I cannot do this.
蜘蛛侠不是什么派对上供人消遣的小把戏 知道吗
Spider-Man is not a party trick, okay?
我做好自己就行
Look, I'm just gonna be myself.
彼得 大家不喜欢这样
Peter, no one wants that.
伙计
Dude.
"屁"得·帕克 你好啊
Penis Parker, what's up?
你那位蜘蛛侠朋友呢
So where's your pal Spider-Man?
让我猜猜 跟你那假想中的女朋友一样在加拿大吗
Let me guess: In Canada with your imaginary girlfriend?
那才不是蜘蛛侠 不过是奈德穿上一件红色的衬衣
That's not Spider-Man. That's just Ned in a red shirt.
"嗨 你们好啊 我是蜘蛛侠
"Hey, what's up? I'm Spider-Man.
我就是过来跟我的兄弟彼得打个照顾
Just thought I'd swing by and say hello to my buddy Peter.
你好啊 奈德 彼得呢
Oh, what's up, Ned? Hey, where's Peter, anyways?
他肯定在这儿..."
He must be around...."
老天 这样好傻啊 我在干嘛
God, this is stupid. What am I doing?
怎么回事
What the hell?
太糟糕了
This sucks.
这个是在从索科维亚回收的一件奥创替代性武器的基础上打造而成
Now, this is crafted from a reclaimed sub-Ultron arm straight from Sokovia.
给 你试试
Here. You try.
我不想要这么高调惹眼的武器 你干嘛要卖我这样的货 伙计
I wanted something low-key. Why are you trying to upsell me, man?
好吧 你想要的我这里也有 行了吧
Okay, okay. I got what you need, all right?
你要的那种货这里多得去了 稍等
I got tons of great stuff here. One sec.
好的 我这里有黑孔手榴弹 齐塔瑞人用的轨道炮...
Okay, I got black hole grenades, Chitauri railguns....
你现在公然放枪 赶紧的
You letting off shots in public now? Hurry up.
听着 时代在变 只有我们在卖这种高科技武器
Look, times are changing. We're the only ones selling these high-tech weapons.
那些抢劫自动取款机的人 肯定是在这里买的武器
This must be where the ATM robbers got their stuff.
我需要能把人粘住不动的武器 我可不想射人穿越时空
I need something to stick up somebody. I'm not trying to shoot them back in time.
我有抗重力攀登鞋
I got antigrav climbers.
攀登鞋
Yo, climbers?
怎么回事
Okay, what the hell is that?
- 你是不是给我们下套了 - 嗨 别这样啊 伙计
- Did you set us up? - Hey, hey, man.
嗨 来啊 你想开枪打人 向我开枪啊
Hey! Hey, come on. You gonna shoot at somebody, shoot at me.
没问题
All right.
怎么回事
What was that?
- 我们得给他打电话 - 不行 不行
- We gotta call him. - No, no, no.
你又开枪了
Did you just do it again?
- 闭嘴 - 我要给他打电话
- Shut up. - I'm calling him.
图姆斯现在不在
Toomes's phone.
头儿 你电话
Boss.
我的屁股
Oh, my butt!
很好 看来我必须抄个近道了
Great. Guess I'm gonna have to take a shortcut.
嗨 伙计们 比赛很精彩 好好玩
Hey, guys. Good game. Have fun.
嗨 小家伙
Hey, hey, buddy.
抱歉 现在没时间跟你玩 给 去捡回来吧
Sorry, no time to play. Here, go fetch.
这样才像话嘛
Now, this is more like it.
好香啊
Smells really good.
电影不错
Great movie!
嗨 你们好
Oh, hey, guys.
别怕
No! No!
嗨 我是彼得 请留言
Hey, it's Peter. Leave a message.
彼得 你在哪儿
Peter, where are you?
这帽子不管用 一点儿都不好玩
The hat's not working. This is not cool.
差点儿抓住你们
Almost got you.
你们以为能这么轻易甩掉我
Thought you got away from me, didn't you?
你们跑到哪儿我都追得上
I got you right where I want you.
惊喜
Surprise!
怎么回事
What the hell?
嗨
Oh, hey.
然后他像个怪物一样俯冲而下
And then he just, like, swooped down like a monster...
一把抓住我 飞到几千英尺高的地方 然后把我扔了下去
and picked me up, and took me up like a thousand feet and just dropped me.
你是怎么找到我的 是不是在我衣服里放了追踪器
How'd you find me? Did you put a tracker in my suit?
我往你衣服里放了很多东西
I put everything in your suit.
包括一个加热器
Including this heater.
这样感觉好多了 谢谢
That's better. Thanks.
你脑子进水了吗
What were you thinking?
那些武器都是那个长翅膀的男的卖出去的 我得把他拿下
The guy with wings is the source of the weapons. I gotta take him down.
你要拿下他 省省吧
Take him down now, huh?
那可是克罗克特炮 有专门的人会负责此事
Crockett, there are people who handle this sort of thing.
- 复仇者吗 - 不 这种小事还轮不到他们出手
- The Avengers? - No. This is a little below their pay grade.
不论如何 斯塔克先生 你没必要亲自过来的
Mr. Stark, you didn't have to come out here.
我应付得来 我没事
I had that. I was fine.
我没有亲自来
Oh, I'm not here.
好在这里有无线网
Thank God this place has Wi-Fi...
不然你现在早就倒大霉了
or you would be toast right now.
你真该烧柱高香 干杯
Thank Ganesh while you're at it. Cheers.
听着 别再管那个会飞的秃鹰男了 拜托
Look, forget the flying vulture guy, please.
- 为什么 - 这还用为什么
- Why? - Why?
因为这是我命令的啊
Because I said so!
抱歉 我在跟一个青少年说话
Sorry, I'm talking to a teenager.
脚踏实地点
Stay close to the ground.
多帮帮那些普通人 比如给你买西班牙油条的老太太
Build up your game helping little people, like that lady that bought you the churro.
你就不能当个友好的
Can't you just be a friendly...
邻家蜘蛛侠
neighborhood Spider-Man?
但我能做的不止这些小事
But I'm ready for more than that now.
不 你还不行
No, you're not.
我跟美国队长较量的时候 你可不是这么想的
That's not what you thought when I took on Captain America.
相信我 孩子 如果队长真想揍扁你 他一定做得到
Trust me, kid. If Cap wanted to lay you out, he would've.
听好了 你要是再遇到那种武器 直接给哈皮打电话
Listen to me. If you come across these weapons again, call Happy.
你在开车吗
Are you driving?
是时候该好好想想上大学的事了
You know, it's never too early to start thinking about college.
麻省理工学院那边我还算说得上话 我挂了
I got some pull at MIT. End call.
不 我不需要上...
No, I don't need to go to...
斯塔克先生已经挂断
Mr. Stark is no longer connected.
好酷啊
That's awesome.
"脚踏实地" 他这话什么意思
"Stay close to the ground"? What is he talking about?
伙计 怎么了 我马上回去
Hey, what's up? I'm on my way back.
其实我打电话 就是让你不要回来了 你听
Actually, I was calling to say maybe you shouldn't come. Listen.
我说"屁得" 你们说"帕克"
When I say "penis," you say "Parker."
- "屁"得 - 帕克
- Penis! - Parker!
抱歉 彼得 看来咱俩还是屌丝
Sorry, Peter. I guess we're still losers.
- 明天见 - 明天学校见
- I'll see you tomorrow. -I'll see you tomorrow in school.
一群蠢货
Idiots.
Idiots!
头儿
Boss?
你老婆一直给你发短信 貌似是刹车灯坏了
Your wife keeps texting you. Something about a brake light.
没跟你说过偷看我手机 会是什么下场吗
What'd I tell you about looking at my phone?
抱歉 你落到这里了
Sorry. You left it out.
你知道我这人天性好奇的
You know I'm a curious person by nature.
那个高海拔真空密封器已经设计好了
I finished designing that high-altitude vacuum seal.
如果你在高空飞行的时候 想要上大号的话
In case you want to, you know, go for the big one?
你还在设计那玩意儿 我跟你说过了 不要
You're still on that? I told you, no.
我不要 算了吧
The answer's no. Forget it.
真是太牛了
I mean, that was badass.
我跟你说过多少次了 不要用那些武器在公共场所开火
How many times have I told you not to fire them out in the open?
- 你说的嘛 扩大销售 - 低调行事
- You said, move the merchandise. - Under the radar.
低调行事
Under the radar!
我们就是这么熬过来的
That's how we survive.
你要是把损害控制部门或者复仇者引来 我们就完蛋了
If you bring Damage Control or the Avengers down here, we're through.
你在外边穿着那身笨蛋衣服 开着汽车
You're out there wearing that goofy thing, lighting up cars...
自称震撼者
calling yourself the Shocker.
"我是震撼者 我令人震撼" 这算什么 专业摔跤
"I'm the Shocker. I shock people." What is this, pro wrestling?
随你怎么说 伙计 得了吧
Whatever, old man. Come on.
听着
Look.
我知道你什么都不在乎
I know you don't give a crap about anything.
但我在乎
But I do.
我辛苦经营这个地方 是因为我有人要照顾
I built this whole place because I got people I have to look after.
随便啦 随便啦
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
你知道吗
You know what?
我再也受不了你这狗屁态度了
I can't afford your bullshit.
- 你走吧 - 你说什么
- Get out of here. - What?
- 你走吧 你被解雇了 - 行啊 没问题
- You're done. You're off the crew. - Yeah, all right.
没问题
All right.
我还真挺想知道 炒了我你能否承受得住呢
Wonder if you can afford me out there, though, right?
毕竟我知道这么多
With everything I know.
- 你说什么 - 我的意思是
- Excuse me? - I'm just saying...
也许你老婆想知道 你的钱究竟是怎么来的
maybe your wife would like to know where you really get your money from.
- 你知道吗 - 怎么了
- You know what? - What?
你说得对
You're right.
- 这东西能用吗 - 我不知道
- That work? - I don't know.
我确实承受不起
I can't afford that.
等一下
Wait.
该死
Damn.
- 我还以为这是抗重力机枪 - 什么
- I thought this was the antigravity gun. - What?
不 是那把
No, that's that one.
给你
Here.
现在你是震撼者 你去把他弄丢的那些武器找回来
Now you're the Shocker. Go out there and find that weapon he lost.
没问题
All right.
谢谢你丢下我跑了
Hey, thanks for bailing on me.
我当时有急事
Yeah, well, something came up.
这是什么
What is that?
不知道 有人想要用它让我蒸发掉
I don't know. Some guy tried to vaporize me with it.
- 真的吗 - 真的
- Seriously? - Yeah.
太牛了
Awesome.
我不是说那人牛 那人简直是小人
I mean, not awesome. Totally uncool of that guy.
好恐怖啊
So scary.
我感觉这是个
Well, look, I think it's...
能量源
a power source.
是啊 但上面连着好多微处理器
Yeah, but it's connected to all these microprocessors.
这是块感应充电板 我的牙刷就是这么充电的
That's an inductive charging plate. That's what I use to charge my toothbrush.
制造武器的人同时运用了外星技术和人类技术
Whoever's making these weapons is combining alien tech with ours.
你刚才说的那句话简直不要太酷
That is literally the coolest sentence anyone has ever said.
我就是想谢谢你让我加入
I just want to thank you for letting me be part of your journey...
这段奇幻旅程...
into this amazing...
手指不要碰到刀片
Keep your fingers clear of the blades.
我一定要弄清楚这玩意儿是什么 还有是谁造的
I gotta figure out what this is and who makes it.
下课后我们去实验室做几个实验
We'll go to the lab after class and run tests.
开干吧
Let's do it.
首先 我们要把这个发光的东西放到质谱仪里
First, we put the glowy thing in the mass spectrometer.
我们得想一个比"发光的东西"更好的名字
We gotta come up with a better name than "glowy thingy."
你说得对
You're right.
糟了
Crap.
过来 过来 快点过来
Come on, come on, come on.
高中校园真是让我不舒服
High schools creep me out.
有种特别古怪的味道
They got this funny smell, you know?
嗨 就是那人想要杀我
Hey, that's one of the guys that tried to kill me.
什么
What?
- 是啊 - 我们得赶紧出去
- Yeah. - We gotta get out of here.
不 我得跟着他们
No, no, no. I gotta follow them.
他们能帮我找到那个把我丢在湖里的家伙
They can lead me to the guy that dropped me in the lake.
- 有人把你丢在了湖里 - 是啊 那感觉糟透了
- Someone dropped you in a lake? - Yeah, it was not good.
- 彼得 - 不 待那儿别动 奈德
- Peter... - No. Stay there, Ned.
彼得
Peter.
你想干嘛
What are you doing?
不干嘛
Nothing.
好 你没事吧
Yeah. You good?
过来一起玩象棋
Chess.
伙计 要是头儿知道我们在这里 你觉得他会怎么说
Man, can you imagine what the boss would say if he knew where we were?
探测器说这里有能量脉冲
It's saying there was an energy pulse here.
没有武器的迹象
There's no sign of the weapon.
即便之前在学校里 现在也不见了
And even if it was here, now it's gone.
那我们也闪人吧
So are we.
太牛了
This is so awesome.
我知道
I know, right?
他们在布鲁克林
They're in Brooklyn.
斯塔顿岛
Staten Island.
他们离开泽西岛了
Leaving Jersey.
他们停了下来
They stopped.
马里兰州
Maryland?
- 那地方有什么 - 我不知道
- What's there? - I don't know.
邪恶老巢
Evil lair?
- 他们还有老巢 - 就凭一群长着翅膀...
- They have a lair? - A gang with alien guns...
拿着外星人武器的家伙 当然
run by a guy with wings? Yeah.
太炫酷了
Badass.
但那里有三百多英里远 你要怎么过去啊
But how are you gonna get there if it's, like, 300 miles away?
那里离华盛顿特区不远
It's not too far from D.C.
- 嗨 彼得来了 - 大家好
- Hey, it's Peter. - Guys.
- 你怎么来了 - 嗨 伙计
- Peter? - Hey, buddy.
我想重新加入你们
I was hoping I could rejoin the team.
不 没门 你不能说走就走
No, no way. You can't quit on us...
然后让我们大家 鼓掌欢迎你再回来
stroll up and be welcomed back by everyone.
嗨 欢迎归队 彼得 弗拉什 你回归第一替补位置
Hey, welcome back! Flash, you're back to first alternate.
- 什么 - 他替了你的位置
- What? - He's taking your place.
抱歉 我们能赶紧出发吗
Excuse me, can we go already?
我晚饭前还想去使馆前参加抗议活动呢
I was hoping to get in some protesting in front of an embassy before dinner.
抗议是爱国的表现 我们上车吧
Protesting is patriotic. Let's get on the bus.
大家请注意 下一个话题是土星的卫星
Focus up. Our next topic is the moons of Saturn.
热力学第二定律
The second law of thermodynamics.
- 法兰克·辛纳屈 - 萨姆特堡
- Frank Sinatra. - Fort Sumter.
- 弗拉什答错了 - 好了 大家注意 下一个话题
- Flash is wrong. - Okay, let's focus. Next one.
莉兹 别让他们太累了
Liz, don't overwork them.
锶 钡 泛合金
Strontium, barium, vibranium.
很好 彼得 你能归队我很开心
Very good, Peter. Glad to have you back.
能回来我也很开心
Glad to be back.
- 目前标准单位... - 我能接个电话吗 很快就好
- What is the current standard unit of...? - Can I take this real quick?
可以
Yeah, fine.
- 喂 - 我屏幕上的亮点在动
- Hello? - Got a blip on my screen here.
你离开纽约了
You left New York?
- 好了 大家请注意 - 追踪器
- Okay, focus up, everyone. - Tracker.
对 就是个学校郊游活动 没什么
Yeah, it's just a school trip. It's nothing.
哈皮 我必须要说 未经同意擅自追踪我
Happy, I gotta say, tracking me without permission...
是对我个人隐私的侵犯
is a complete violation of privacy.
- 那不一样 - 什么不一样
- That's different. - What's different?
没什么 我就是去参加学术十项全能大赛
Nothing. Look, it's just the Academic Decathlon.
- 不是什么大事儿 - 嗨 大不大我说了算
- It's no big deal. - Hey, hey. I'll decide if it's no big deal.
听起来不是什么大事 但你给我记住了 我看着你呢
Sounds like no big deal, but remember, I'm watching you.
- 大家跟紧了 - 好的
- Everyone stick together. - Yeah.
不是吧 这地方好大啊
You kidding me? This place is huge.
- 我见过更大的地方 - 这里有只鸟
- I've seen bigger. - There's a bird in here.
- 嗨 你拿笔记本电脑了 对吧 - 怎么了
- Hey, you brought your laptop, right? - Why?
彼得
Peter...
我们为什么要把追踪器从你的战服里拿掉
why are we removing the tracker from your suit?
因为我必须在这些人再次转移之前 找到他们的头儿
I gotta follow these guys to their boss before they move again...
而且我不想让斯塔克先生知道
and I don't really want Mr. Stark to know about it.
这么说你在骗钢铁侠
So you're lying to Iron Man now?
不 我没在骗他
No, I'm not lying.
他只是不明白 我现在能做的事情很多
He just doesn't really get what I can do yet.
好了
Gotcha.
好了 哈皮 尽情享受追踪这个台灯吧
All right, Happy, enjoy tracking this lamp.
这里有无数个子系统
There's a ton of other subsystems in here...
但都被《训练轮协议》禁用了
but they're all disabled by the Training Wheels Protocol.
怎么了
What?
"《训练轮协议》" 快关掉
"Training Wheels Protocol"? Turn it off.
我觉得这样不好 这些子系统之所以被禁用 是有原因的
I don't think that's a good idea. They're blocked for a reason.
拜托 伙计 我才不需要什么训练轮
Come on, man, I don't need training wheels.
他们总是把我当孩子 真烦
I'm sick of him treating me like a kid all the time.
- 一点儿都不酷 - 但你就是个孩子啊
- It's not cool. - But you are a kid.
一个可以徒手拦住公共汽车的孩子
A kid who can stop a bus with his bare hands.
彼得 我就是觉得这主意不好 万一这么做违法呢
Peter, I just don't think this is a great idea. I mean, what if this is illegal?
听着 拜托了 这是我证明自己的机会
Look, please. This is my chance to prove myself.
我应付得了 奈德 拜托了
I can handle it. Ned, come on.
- 我真心觉得这么做不好 - 技术特工
- I don't think this is a good idea. - The guy in the chair.
- 别诱惑我 - 拜托了
- Don't do that. - Come on.
那个发光的东西是证据 一定要保管好了
The glowy thing, it's evidence. Keep it safe.
- 知道了吗 - 知道了
- All right? - Okay. Okay.
- 他们又移动了 - 当心
- They're moving. - Be careful.
- 嗨 莉兹 - 你来得刚好
- Hey, Liz. - Perfect timing.
我们要去游泳
We're gonna go swimming.
- 来啊 来啊 - 什么
- Come on, come on, come on. - What?
- 嗨 彼得 - 嗨
- Hey, Peter. - Hi.
嗨
Hey.
我正要...正要去商务中心学习
I was... I was gonna go study in the business center.
没这个必要 你是我见过的最聪明的人
You don't need to. You're the smartest guy I've ever met.
而且
And besides...
比赛前大家一起放纵一下 有助于提高士气
a rebellious group activity the day before competition is good for morale.
这是我从TED演讲里听来的 所以...
Well, I read that in a TED Talk, so...
我...我是从TED演讲里听来的
I... I heard it in a TED Talk.
我看过一本辅导书
And I read a coaching book.
你真的...你真的很看重这个比赛
You really... This is really important to you.
是啊 关乎到我们的未来
Yeah. It's our future.
我不会搞砸的
I'm not gonna screw it up.
我们还把小冰箱洗劫一空 这些糖果棒差不多有11美元吧
Besides, we raided the minibar and these candy bars were, like, $11.
穿上你的泳裤 跟我们一起玩儿吧
So get your trunks on and come on.
- 快点 - 我来了
- Come on. - I'm coming, I'm coming.
我们走
Let's go.
- 晚上好 彼得 - 喂
- Good evening, Peter. - Hello? Hello?
恭喜你完成《训练轮协议》
Congratulations on completing the Training Wheels Protocol...
并获得权限开启服装全部功能
and gaining access to your suit's full capabilities.
谢谢
Thank you.
今晚我们去哪儿
Where would you like to take me tonight?
我们一个人身上放了追踪器 他是个大坏蛋
I put a tracker on someone. He's a bad guy.
发现追踪器
Tracker located.
正在设计路线以拦截目标
Plotting course to intercept target.
好的 只要能让我赶回来参加比赛 一切都无所谓
As long as I make it back in time for decathlon, it's fine.
距离目的地一百米 接近目标
One hundred meters from destination and closing.
现在跳车
Jump now.
发现三个人
Detecting three individuals.
他们的秘密老巢为何在加油站 简直傻透了
Why is their secret lair in a gas station? That's so lame.
嗨 制服女士 他们在干嘛
Hey, suit lady, what are they doing?
你想知道他们在说什么吗
Do you want to hear what they're saying?
我能听他们在说什么吗 好啊
I can hear what they're saying? Yeah.
开启增强版侦查模式
Activating Enhanced Reconnaissance Mode.
铁手套是清理拉各斯的时候弄来的 其他都出自我的设计
I got the gauntlet from the Lagos cleanup. The rest is my design.
哇 好酷啊
Whoa, that's so cool.
真不敢相信他们还在清理三飞饰那堆垃圾
Can't believe they're still cleaning up that Triskelion mess.
挺好啊 只要他们一直制造垃圾 我们就能一直赚钱
I love it. They keep making messes, we keep getting rich.
进入目标
Target inbound.
他们正在实施抢劫
They're in the middle of a heist.
我可以当场抓获他们 太棒了
I could catch them red-handed. This is awesome.
好的 我需要再接近一些 才能看清楚实际情况
Okay, I'll get closer to see what's happening.
你是否希望我转换到增强版战斗模式
Would you like me to engage Enhanced Combat Mode?
"增强版战斗模式" 好啊
"Enhanced Combat Mode"? Yeah.
启动"秒杀"功能
Activating Instant Kill.
不 不 我不想杀人
No, no, no. I don't want to kill anybody.
关闭"秒杀"功能
Deactivating Instant Kill.
听到没
Did you hear that?
刚才到底是怎么回事
What the hell just happened? What was that?
你从标志那里跳了下去 摔了个狗吃屎
You jumped off the sign and landed on your face.
我的射网器怎么用不了了
What's wrong with my web-shooters?
速射是增强版战斗模式的默认发射模式
Rapid-fire is the default for Enhanced Combat Mode.
我要速射干嘛
Why would I need rapid-fire?
你需要更多选择吗
Would you like to see more options?
一共有576种射网组合模式供你挑选
You have 576 possible web-shooter combinations.
斯塔克先生实在是搞得太复杂了
Mr. Stark really overdid it.
你们两个在这儿等着
You two wait right here.
等下 你还是打开减震器比较好
Wait. You're gonna want to turn on the dampers.
不然那东西会把你胳膊震掉
That thing will shatter your arm.
好的 减震器在哪儿
All right, where's the dampers?
- 那个吧 - 选得好
- That one. - Great choice.
希望我帮你把这个设置成新的默认模式吗
Would you like me to set this as your new default?
不 不 不
No, no, no.
- 把它推进去 不 那个... - 这里 这个
- Push that in. No, the other... - Here? This one here?
- 那是什么 - 电击网
- What was that? - Taser webs.
电击网 我不要电击网
Taser webs? I don't want Taser webs.
你貌似并不了解射网器的设置
You seem to be unfamiliar with your web-shooter settings.
要不要复习一下
Would you like to run a refresher course?
- 不用了 你选就好了 - 没问题
- No. Just... You choose. - Sure thing.
6A9号 你能准时到达吗
Six-alpha-niner, are you running on time?
中心部门 收到 6A9号会按时到达
Copy, central. Six-alpha-niner on schedule.
- 目标出现 - 出击
- I got a visual. - Green light, green light.
就是他
Oh, that's him.
好的 我来盯着护卫队
Okay. I got eyes on the convoy.
停在守车后边
Pulling in behind the caboose.
部署挂锚
Deploy anchors.
投入
Dropping down.
没有外发呼救信号 你们都很安全
No outgoing distress signals. You're clear.
嗨 看来这里有些好东西
Hey. Looks like they got some good stuff here.
真酷 像是某种物质移相器
Cool. It's like some kind of matter phase shifter.
好了 我上去了
All right, coming up.
嗨 鸟人 这不是你的东西
Hey, Big Bird. This doesn't belong to you.
天呐
Oh, God.
- 制服女士 怎么回事 - 是你让我选的
- Suit lady, what was that?! - You told me to choose.
什么 不要 一切恢复正常状态
What? No, just set everything back to normal.
启动所有系统
Activating all systems.
我的头好疼
My head.
你好像有轻微脑震荡
You appear to have a mild concussion.
嗨 我这是在哪儿
Hey, so where am I right now?
我不知道
I'm not sure.
集装箱四壁挡住了传感器的信号
The container walls are hindering my sensors.
稍等
Wait a minute.
他们肯定是劫持了卡车 要把我带去他们的邪恶老巢
They must have hijacked the truck and taken me to their evil lair.
好的 制服女士 我们得想办法出去
Okay, suit lady, we're gonna have to fight our way out of this one.
三 二 一
Three, two, one.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
制服女士 这是什么地方
Suit lady, where am I?
你目前是在东海岸最安全的设施内
You're in the most secure facility on the eastern seaboard.
损害控制部门地下储藏室
The Damage Control deep storage vault.
不是吧 真的吗
No. Seriously?
大门明早才会有人打开
The door will most likely remain closed until morning.
明天早上
Morning?
嗨 制服女士 我感觉叫你"制服女士"挺不礼貌的
Hey, suit lady. I kind of feel bad calling you "suit lady," you know?
我应该给你起个名字
I think I should probably give you a name.
比如说莉兹 不 不行
Like Liz. No, no, no.
老天 真是...太奇怪了
God, that's... That's weird.
那凯伦呢
What about Karen?
如果你喜欢 可以叫我凯伦
You can call me Karen if you would like.
嗨 凯伦 这衣服还有什么功能
Hey, Karen, what else can this suit do?
怎么了
What?
也许我们应该好好复习一下
Maybe we should run that refresher course.
- 弹跳网 - 弹跳网
- Ricochet web. -Ricochet web.
- 酷 - 分隔蛛网
- Cool. - Splitter web.
- 蛛液手榴弹 - 蛛液手榴弹
- Web grenade. -Web grenade!
我要不要告诉莉兹我就是蜘蛛侠
Should I tell Liz that I'm Spider-Man?
莉兹是谁
Who is Liz?
莉兹是谁 她是...
Who's Liz? She's...
她是最好的姑娘 超级赞
She's the best. She's awesome.
她就是我一个同学
She's just a girl who goes to my school.
而且...
And...
是的 我真的很想告诉她 但那么做的话有点怪怪的 你懂吗
Yeah, I just... I really want to tell her, but it's kind of weird, you know?
"嗨 我是蜘蛛侠"
"Hey, I'm Spider-Man."
这有什么奇怪的
What's weird about that?
万一她期待的是托尼·斯塔克呢
What if she's expecting someone like Tony Stark?
试想一下 如果她看到是我 心里该有多失望
Imagine how disappointed she'd be when she sees me.
如果我是她的话 一点儿都不会失望
Well, if I were her, I wouldn't be disappointed at all.
谢了 凯伦
Thanks, Karen.
有个人说说话真好
It's really nice to have somebody to talk to.
我们在这里多久了
Hey, how long we been here anyways?
- 37分钟 - 什么
- Thirty-seven minutes. -What?!
才37分钟 不是吧
Thirty-seven minutes? That's insane.
我受不了了 我一定...一定要想个办法出去
I cannot take this anymore. I got to... I gotta get out of here.
这里肯定有能用得上的东西
There's got to be something in here I can use.
我瞧瞧
Okay, let's see.
不行
Nope.
好酷啊
That's awesome.
嗨 这个跟那个发光的东西很像嘛
Hey, it's like the glowy thing.
你手里那个发光的东西 是一个齐塔瑞爆炸能量核
That glowy thing is an explosive Chitauri energy core.
你是说我们一直背着一个炸弹跑来跑去
You mean, we've been carrying around a bomb?
它只有受到辐射时才会爆炸
It would require radiation to transform it into an explosive state.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
嗨 有人吗 快来人救我 嗨
Hey! Please! Please, somebody let me out! Hey!
凯伦 你得帮我把时间锁改写一下
Karen, you have to help me override that time lock.
好的 凯伦 降低电压 试一下
Okay, Karen, lower the voltage and run it.
试验失败
Trial unsuccessful.
我们需要把所有序列都试一次
Okay, we're just gonna have to try every sequence.
奈德 彼得 我们要迟到了 快点 得出发了
Ned, Peter, we're gonna be late. Come on, let's go.
好的 先等一下
Okay. Hold on, hold on.
开始第247次试验
Initiating trial 247.
成功了 成功了
It worked. It works.
请关闭手机
Please be sure all cell phones are turned off.
谢谢
Thank you.
凯伦 你得赶紧把我送到十项全能比赛现场
Karen, get me to decathlon as fast as possible.
没问题 告诉我地点就好
Sure thing. Just tell me where it is.
就在华盛顿纪念碑对面那条街上
Across the street from the Washington Monument.
我是奈德 请留言
It's Ned. Leave a message.
奈德 赶紧打过来 那个发光体是个炸弹
Ned. Call me back. The glowy thing's a bomb!
你右侧有一辆汽车正在靠近
There's a vehicle approaching on your right.
接下来一分定胜负
We have now entered sudden death.
答对下一个问题的团队会获得冠军
The next correct answer wins the championship.
中城科技队
Midtown Tech?
零
Zero.
答对了
That is correct.
中城队获得冠军
Midtown takes the championship.
- 我们赢了 - 我真为你们感到自豪
- We won. - You guys, I am so proud of you.
我都跟你说了我们不需要彼得
Told you we didn't need Peter.
弗拉什 你一个问题都没答
Flash, you didn't answer a question.
- 你这就参观完了 米歇尔 - 是的 我只是...
- Taking it all in, Michelle? - Oh, yeah, I just...
我不喜欢庆祝由奴隶建造的东西
I don't want to celebrate something that was built by slaves.
我肯定华盛顿纪念碑不是由...
I'm sure the Washington Monument wasn't built by...
好吧
Okay.
- 那你好好看书吧 - 谢谢
- Enjoy your book. - Thanks.
- 奈德 你还活着啊 - 彼得 你还好吧
- Oh, Ned, you're alive. - Peter, are you okay?
那个发光的东西呢 在哪儿
Where's the glowy thing? The glowy thing?
别担心 它很安全 在我背包里
Don't worry. It's safe. It's in my backpack.
奈德 听着 那个东西很危险
Ned, listen, the glowy thing is dangerous.
你错过了十项全能大赛 我替你挡过去了
You missed the decathlon. I covered for you.
- 听我说 - 我们在华盛顿纪念碑
- Listen to me. - We're at the Washington Monument.
- 彼得 是你吗 - 嗨 莉兹
- Peter, is that you? - Hey, Liz.
- 是莉兹吗 - 让奈德接电话
- Is that Liz? - Put Ned back on the phone.
你应该把心里的感觉告诉她
You should tell her how you feel.
你太不靠谱了 我们能赢算你走运
You flake. You are lucky we won.
我很想生气 但我更担心 你到底是怎么了
I want to be mad, but I'm more worried. Like, what is going on with you?
莉兹 我有很重要的事情 必须告诉奈德
Liz, I have to talk to Ned. It's important.
请将所有物品放到传送带上
Miss. All items on the belt, please.
奈德背包里有个东西
There's something in Ned's backpack.
特别危险 千万别让它接触到X射线
It's dangerous. Don't let it go through x-ray.
莉兹 莉兹 该死
Liz? Liz! Damn it.
能让我告诉彼得他被驱逐出团队了吗
Can I be the one to tell Peter he's expelled?
华盛顿纪念碑有555英尺 五右八分之一英寸高
The Washington Monument is 555 feet, five and one-eighth inches tall.
请大家注意这些大理石和花岗岩的切割方式
Notice how the marble and granite are cut around the stone.
不 凯伦 那是怎么回事
No, no, no. Karen, what's going on up there?
齐塔瑞核已经分解
The Chitauri core has detonated...
致使电梯结构出现了几处结构性损坏
and caused severe structural damage to the elevator.
- 不要啊 - 我的朋友在上面
- Oh, no. - My friends are up there.
什么 别担心 女士 不会有事的
What? Don't worry, ma'am, everything's gonna be okay.
借过 借过一下 老天 可真高啊
Excuse me, excuse me. Oh, my God, that's tall.
天呐 看看电梯顶
Oh, my God. Look at the ceiling.
大家都冷静
Just stay calm, everyone.
我们都要死在这里了
Oh, we are all going to die here.
距离灾难性故障发生还有十分钟
Estimating 10 minutes before catastrophic failure.
我们都要完蛋了
We're freaking screwed.
我知道大家都很害怕 但我们的安全系统在运行中
Okay, I know that was scary, but our safety systems are working.
安全系统完全失效
The safety systems are completely failing.
我们在这里很安全
We're very safe in here.
电梯里的人命悬一线
The occupants are in imminent mortal danger.
我已经全速开跑了
Going as fast as I can!
- 上来 - 把你的手给我
- Let's go. - Give me your hand.
距离灾难性故障发生还有125秒
You now have 125 seconds until catastrophic failure.
什么 为什么
What?! Why?
能量核突然位移 导致转化速度加快
Unexpected motion has caused the deterioration to escalate.
- 我要怎么进去 - 启动侦查无人机
- How do I get in there? - Activating reconnaissance drone.
我身上一直戴着这东西吗 太棒了
Has that been there this whole time? That's awesome.
定位最佳进入点
Locating optimal entry point.
前往西南窗口
Proceed to southwest window.
凯伦 我这就出发
Karen, I'm on my way.
- 这里有好多碎玻璃啊 - 你行的
- There's a lot of glass here. - You got this.
加油 坚持住
Keep coming, keep coming.
好了 我的天啊
Okay. Oh, my God.
好的
Okay.
怎么了 你到达西南窗口了
What's wrong? You've reached the southwest window.
- 为什么犹豫 - 没事
- Why are you hesitating? - It's fine.
我只是从未到过这么高的地方
I've just never been this high before.
你还没有重新设置降落伞系统
You have also not reinstalled your parachute...
不小心从这个高度摔下去很可能会致命
so a fall from this height would most likely be lethal.
真会挑时候
Perfect.
我的天
Oh, my God.
这玻璃怎么就不碎呢
Why is it not breaking?
这是厚度约为四英寸的防弹玻璃 你得制造更大的冲力
It's four-inch ballistic glass. You'll have to create more momentum.
我们是华盛顿警察 表明你的身份
This is D.C. Metro Police. Identify yourself.
我朋友困在里面 住手
My friends are in there! Stop!
立刻回到地面上
Return to the ground immediately.
- 好吧 下一个是谁 - 是我 该我了
- Okay, who's next? - Me, it's my turn.
弗拉什 你有没有搞错 你在干嘛
Flash, seriously? What are you doing?
- 快点 - 别管奖杯了
- Come on. - Don't worry about the trophy.
下去
Stand down!
立刻回到地面上
Return to the ground immediately.
下去 否则我们就开枪了
Return to the ground or we will open fire!
往上 往上
Go up, go up.
我搞得定的
I got this.
拿好我的奖杯
Take my trophy.
这是你最后的机会
This is your last chance.
我要死了
I'm gonna die.
碎吧
Break!
我成功了
I did it.
嘿 你们还好吗 别担心 我来救你们了
Hey, how you doing? Don't worry. I got you.
- 太棒了 - 嘿 嘿 当心
- Yes! Yes. - Hey, hey, hey.
- 大块头 别乱动 - 抱歉 先生
- Big guy, quit moving around. - I'm sorry, sir.
快点 我们走了
Let's go, let's go!
好了 可以了
Okay, okay.
- 哈灵顿先生 快出去 - 跟上 奈德
- Mr. Harrington, go. - Ned, come on.
- 你们到站了 - 快出来 莉兹
- This is your stop. - Come on, Liz.
快点 所有人都出去 快点出去 大家都快出去
Go, go, go. Everybody out. Move it, people. Move it, move it.
- 你确定这安全吗 - 莉兹
- Are you sure it's safe? - Liz.
莉兹
Liz!
我抓住你了 你没事了
You're okay. You're okay.
好的
Okay.
- 我的天啊 - 很好 很好
- Oh, my God. - Good, good.
使劲往上拉 加油 你们几个 往后退
Come on up. Come on, you guys, stay back.
- 拉上来了 - 你们没事吧
- Come on in. - You guys good?
大家都没事吧
So is everyone okay?
你的机会来了 彼得
This is your chance, Peter.
吻她
Kiss her.
谢谢
Thank you.
你真的是彼得·帕克的朋友
Are you really friends with Peter Parker?
我可以完成下一个订单 但没有那辆卡车里的新材料...
I can finish the next order, but without any new materials from that truck....
是啊 真该死
Yeah, damn it.
但我们手里的材料还足够完成加尔冈的订单 对吗
We still have enough to do the Gargan deal though, right?
是的 但之后的订单就做不成了
Yeah, but then that's it.
不如我还是继续打造高海拔真空密封器吧
Maybe it is time that I built the high-altitude seal.
- 你能不能闭上嘴 别说这事了 - 我们只能做这个了
- Would you shut up about that? - It's only one job.
不
No.
八年了 那些联邦工作人员 丝毫没有察觉
Eight years, not a word from the feds, nothing from those...
斯塔克大厦里那些一副万圣节打扮的傻蛋们也是一样
Halloween-costume-wearing bozos up there in Stark Tower.
然后突然之间不知从哪冒出来一个穿着红色紧身衣的小混蛋
And then all of a sudden, this little bastard in red tights shows up.
妄想能毁掉我创造的一切
And he thinks he can tear down everything I've built.
真的吗
Really?
我要宰了他
I'm gonna kill him.
- 我会找到他... - 我找到他了
- I'm gonna find him... - Found him.
蜘蛛侠从天而降
The Spider-Man swooped in...
英勇地救下了一支来自皇后区的参赛队伍
heroically saving an Academic Decathlon team from Queens.
这位戴面具的英雄仍旧身份不明
The identity of the masked hero is still unknown.
- 妈妈 - 孩子们 没事了
- Mom. - Oh, kids. All right.
彼得 过来 快过来
Peter. Come here, come here, come here.
上周末 来自中城的学术十项全能队伍
This past weekend, Midtown's Academic Decathlon team...
击败了全国头号种子队伍 赢得了全国冠军
defeated the country's best to win the national championship.
就在那一天的晚些时候 他们也击败了死亡
Later that day, they also defeated death.
突如其来的爆炸 萨利在尖叫 弗拉什在尖叫 大家都在尖叫
Explosion. Sally scream. Flash scream. Everybody screaming.
当时到处是紫色的激光和烟雾 气氛超紧张 就像邦乔维乐队的音乐会
There were purple lasers and smoke. It was **** tight, like a Bon Jovi concert.
如你所知 我们成功逃出生天 这点是最重要的
As you know, we made it out alive, and that's the important thing.
我承受不了在学校组织的旅行中失去哪怕一个学生
I couldn't bear to lose a student on a school trip.
这事不能再次发生
Not again.
幸亏有蜘蛛侠 没人受到严重伤害 我对此满怀感激
Thankfully, no one was seriously injured thanks to the Spider-Man.
- 谢谢你 蜘蛛侠 - 谢谢你 蜘蛛侠
- Thank you, Spider-Man. - Thank you, Spider-Man.
接下来是 蜘蛛侠狂热潮席卷整个校园
Up next: the Spider-Man mania is sweeping the school.
如何彰显你的蜘蛛侠精神
How can you show your spider spirit?
哥们 哥们
Dude, dude, dude.
你火了 但没人知道火的人就是你 这感觉如何
What is it like being famous when nobody knows it's you?
- 棒极了 伙计 - 棒极了
- Crazy, dude. - It's crazy.
- 我们该把真相告诉大家吗 - 不行
- Should we tell everyone? - No.
- 我该把真相告诉大家吗 - 不行 哥们 这主意不好
- Should I tell everyone? - No, dude. That's not a good idea.
- 好了 走吧 我们上课要迟到了 - 我不打算去上课
- Okay, come on, we'll be late to class. - I'm not going to class.
你逃掉十项全能比赛 已经给人惹上麻烦了
You're already in trouble for ditching the decathlon.
哥们 听着 我会解决好的
Dude, listen, I figured it out.
那个穿着飞行服的家伙 从损害控制部门那里偷东西
The wingsuit guy is stealing from Damage Control.
他从损害控制部门那里偷来的东西 让他制造出了那些武器
What he takes from Damage Control, that's how he builds the weapons.
- 所以我要做的就是抓住他 - 但我们还有个西语随堂测验
- So all I gotta do is catch him. - But we have a Spanish quiz.
奈德 我大概永远都不会回学校了
Ned, I'm probably never gonna come back here.
斯塔克先生要招新人加入复仇者联盟
Mr. Stark is moving the Avengers upstate...
- 当我抓住那个家伙交给他的时候... - 哥们
- so when I bring this guy in... - Dude.
你想高中就辍学
You want to be a high school dropout?
我现在的能力已经远远超出高中水平了
I am so far beyond high school right now.
帕克 到我办公室来
Parker, my office.
看来
So...
你被留堂了
you got detention.
你做了错事 也清楚你做了错事
You screwed up. You know what you did was wrong.
问题是你打算如何弥补自己的错误
The question is, how are you gonna make things right?
也许你当时只是想扮酷
Maybe you were trying to be cool.
但是请听我这个扮酷到在冰里冻了65年的人一言
But take it from a guy who's been frozen for 65 years...
扮酷的唯一办法就是遵守规则
the only way to really be cool is to follow the rules.
我们都知道什么是对的 什么是错的
We all know what's right. We all know what's wrong.
下回那些弱智再想怂恿你去做一些
Next time those turkeys try to convince you of something...
- 你明知是错的事 - 你要去哪 回来
- you know is wrong... - Where you going? Get back here.
自己先好好自忖一下 美国队长会怎么做
just think to yourself, what would Captain America do?
你怎么在这 你又没被留堂
Why are you here? You don't have detention.
我知道 我只是想来这里 给处于危机中的人画个素描
Oh, I know. I just like coming here to sketch people in crisis.
这人就是你
It's you.
你们的身体正在改变 相信我 我知道这种感觉
So your body's changing. Believe me, I know how that feels.
梅婶婶
May?
嘿 凯伦 你好吗
Hey, Karen. What's up?
嘿 彼得 你的西语测验考得怎么样
Hey, Peter. How was your Spanish quiz?
能不能帮我个忙
I was wondering if you could help me.
我想搞清楚那晚桥下的那些人是谁
I'm trying to figure out who the guys under the bridge were that night...
但我只记得车牌号的一部分
but I can only remember part of a license plate.
我可以对那次接触拍下的影像做个面部识别
I can run facial recognition on the footage of that encounter.
- 影像 - 是的 彼得
- Footage? - Yes, Peter.
你看到的一切我都会录下来
I record everything you see.
- 一切 - 一切
- Everything? - Everything.
- 一直都是 - 这叫做"婴儿监视器协议"
- All the time? - It's called the Baby-Monitor Protocol.
哦 当然啦
Yeah, of course it is.
- 把录像时间倒回上周五 - 乐意之至
- Yeah, just roll it back to last Friday. - With pleasure.
嘿 大家好 特攻联盟大聚会了
Hey, everyone. Yeah, kick-ass party.
嘿 你好吗 莉兹 彼得跟我说过很多关于你的事
Hey, what's up, Liz? Peter's told me a lot about you.
不是这个 这只是我在瞎胡闹
No, no, no. This is just me messing around.
把时间转到那天晚点的时候
Go later in the day, later in the day.
是我 索尔 奥丁之子
It is I, Thor, son of Odin.
不 不对 这绝对...
No, no, no. That's definitely...
这绝对不是我们想要看的
That's definitely not what we wanted to watch.
- 你的滑稽模仿很有趣 - 快进到武器交易那里
- Your impressions are very funny. - Fast-forward to the arms deal.
好的
Okay.
- 右边的那两个是谁 - 正在搜索执法部门数据库
- The two on the right, who are they? - Searching law enforcement databases.
没有找到这两个人的记录
No records found for two of the individuals.
- 什么也没找到 - 一个人的身份已查明
- Nothing? - One individual identified.
亚伦·戴维斯 年龄33岁
Aaron Davis, age 33.
记录中有他的一个犯罪记录和一个位于皇后区的地址
He has a criminal record and an address here in Queens.
我们去拜访他一下
Let's pay him a visit.
你想要我激活"强化审讯协议"吗
Would you like me to activate the Enhanced Interrogation Protocol?
好啊
Yeah.
- 还记得我吗 - 嘿
- Remember me? - Hey...
我需要些信息 你必须马上给我
I need information. You'll give it to me now.
- 好吧 冷静 - 快给我
- All right, chill. - Come on!
- 你的声音怎么了 - 你这话是什么意思
- What happened to your voice? - What do you mean?
我那天在桥下听到过你的声音 我知道女孩的声音是什么样
I heard you by the bridge. I know what a girl sound like.
我不是女孩 我是男孩 我是说 我是...我是个男人
I'm not a girl. I'm a boy. I mean, I'm a... I'm a man.
我不在乎你是谁 是男还是女
I don't care what you are, a boy, a girl...
我不是女孩 我是男人
I'm not a girl. I'm a man.
行了 哥们 听着 是谁在销售那些武器
Come on, man. Look, who is selling these weapons?
我必须知道 告诉我他们的名字 或其他什么的
I need to know. Give me names or else.
- 你以前从没做过这种事 对吧 - 关闭审讯模式
- You ain't ever done this before, huh? - Deactivate Interrogation Mode.
听我说 哥们
Look, man.
那些家伙在销售超级危险的武器
These guys are selling weapons that are crazy dangerous.
那种武器不能出现在街头
They can't be out on the streets.
要是其中的一个武器能把德尔马熟食杂货店切成两半
If one of them can cut Delmar's Bodega in half...
- 你知道德尔马熟食杂货店 - 当然 他家有全皇后区最棒的三明治
- You know Delmar's? - Yeah, best sandwich in Queens.
- 潜艇避风塘也不错 - 太多面包
- Sub Haven's pretty good. - It's too much bread.
- 我喜欢吃面包 - 拜托 哥们 请你告诉我
- I like bread. - Come on, man, please.
愚蠢的审讯系统 凯伦 再也别这么做了
Stupid Interrogation Mode. Karen, don't ever do that again.
那天晚上 你对那个家伙说 "如果你要开枪 那就朝我来"
The other night, you told that dude, "If you shoot somebody, shoot me."
这可真有胆
That's pretty ballsy.
我不想那些武器出现在这个街区
I don't want those weapons in this neighborhood.
我有个侄子就住在那里
I got a nephew who live here.
那些人是谁
Who are these guys?
关于那个穿着飞行服的家伙 你有什么信息可以告诉我
What can you tell me about the guy with the wings?
除了他是个打扮得像恶魔的疯子之外 我什么也不知道
Other than he's a psychopath dressed like a demon, nothing.
我不知道他是谁 也不知道他在哪
I don't know who he is or where he is.
- 但我的确知道他会去哪 - 真的
- I do know where he's gonna be. - Really?
真的 这个我以前和他共事的疯子
Yeah, this crazy dude I used to work with...
他应该在和他做交易
he's supposed to be doing a deal with him.
太好了 好极了
Yes! Yes.
- 谢谢 - 嘿 等等
- Thank... - Hey. Hey. Hey.
我还没告诉你地点 你不知道他们的位置
I didn't tell you where. You don't have a location.
对啊 没错 我的错 太傻了 请你...
Right, of course. Yeah, my bad. Silly. Just...
没错
Yeah.
- 交易地点在哪里 - 我能给你个建议吗
- Where is it? - Can I give you some advice?
在这方面你得改进一下
You got to get better at this part of the job.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我很吓人的
I'm intimidating.
- 斯塔顿岛渡轮 11点 - 没多久了啊
- Staten Island Ferry, 11. - Oh, that's soon.
这个蛛网会在两小时后溶解
That's gonna dissolve in two hours.
不 不行 赶紧把这个弄掉
No, no, no. Come fix this.
- 等两个小时吧 这是你应得的 - 我这里面还有冰淇淋呢
- Two hours. You deserve that. - I got ice cream in here.
这是你应得的 你是个罪犯 再见 罪犯先生
You deserve that. You're a criminal. Bye, Mr. Criminal.
不错
Nice.
好了 凯伦 启动强化侦察模式
Okay, Karen, activate Enhanced Reconnaissance Mode.
没问题
Sure thing.
他坐在客舱的最前面
He's up front, main deck.
我讨厌这个家伙
I hate this guy.
他是那桥下的那个人 对面另一个人是谁
It's the guy from the bridge, right? Who's that other guy?
查到后及时告诉我
Just keep me posted.
我的罪犯数据库里没有他的记录
There's no record of him in my criminal database.
梅·帕克来电 是否转接入你的头部显示器
Incoming call from May Parker. Should I reroute to your heads-up display?
我现在不能接电话 待会给她回电话
I can't talk right now. I'll call her back.
嘿 小无人机 盯着那个家伙 这回我们不能放跑任何人
Hey, dronie, keep an eye on that guy. We can't let anybody get away this time.
- 左边那个人是谁 - 麦克·加根盖尔
- Who's the guy on the left? - Mac Gargan.
前科累累 包括谋杀罪
Extensive criminal record, including homicide.
要我启动秒杀模式吗
Would you like me to activate Instant Kill?
不 凯伦 别再建议秒杀模式了
No, Karen, stop it with the Instant Kill already.
白色皮卡车
White pickup truck.
小无人机 扫描整艘船 找出一辆白色皮卡车
Dronie, scan the ship for a white pickup truck.
这真是太棒了
Oh, this is too perfect.
武器 买家和卖家都欢聚一堂了
I got the weapons, buyers and sellers in one place.
- 托尼·斯塔克来电 - 不 不 别接
- Incoming call from Tony Stark. - No, no, no.
- 别接 - 帕克先生 能聊聊吗
- Don't answer. - Mr. Parker. Got a sec?
- 其实 我在学校呢 - 不 你没有
- I'm actually at school. - No, you're not.
- 你在华盛顿做得不错 - 好的
- Nice work in D.C. - Okay.
我爸爸其实从未给过我很多支持
My dad never really gave me a lot of support...
我想要打破这个可耻的惯例
and I'm trying to break the cycle of shame.
我正忙着呢
I'm in the middle of something.
别在我夸奖你的时候打断我
Don't cut me off when I'm complimenting you.
总之 有好事要... 那是什么
Anyway, great things are about to... What is that?
是我的乐队在练习
I'm at band practice.
这可真奇怪 哈皮告诉我 你六周前退出了乐队 怎么回事
That's odd. Happy told me you quit band six weeks ago. What's up?
- 我得挂了 结束通话 - 嘿
- I gotta go. End call. - Hey.
归我了
I'll take those!
嘿 伙计们 非法武器交易那艘渡轮是10点30分那班 你们错过了
Hey, guys. The illegal weapons-deal ferry was at 10:30. You missed it.
蜘蛛人来了
Spider guy's here.
别这么急
Not so fast.
你们还好吧 是我不好 劲用得有点大了
Are you guys okay? My bad. That was a little hard.
我得说 另一个家伙更会用这玩意
I got to say, the other guy was way better with that thing.
我真诚地...
I'm honestly...
我...我太震惊了
I'm... I'm shocked.
- 别动 我们是联邦调查局 - 别动
- Freeze! FBI. - Don't move.
- 趴到地上 - 我们是联调局
- Get on the ground. - FBI.
你们说联调局是什么意思
What do you mean, FBI?
- 他们是美国联邦调查局 - 我知道 但他们来这儿干嘛
- The Federal Bureau of Investigation. - I know, but what are they doing here?
让开 快让开
Get out of the way. Get out of the way!
不
No.
小心 小心 让开 快让开
Look out, look out, look out. Move, move, move!
- 让开 - 到顶层甲板上去
- Move. - Get to the top deck.
我们要离开这里
We're getting out of here.
启动电击网
Activate Taser web!
你在和你不了解的东西作对
You're messing with things you don't understand.
我的天啊 我做了什么 凯伦
Oh, my God. What do I do? Karen...
X光扫描整艘船 标出所有最坚固的支撑点
give me an x-ray of the boat and target all the strongest points.
蛛液手榴弹 蛛液手榴弹
Web grenade. Web grenade.
分隔蛛网 快点
Splitter web, go.
干得好 彼得 你成功了 百分之九十八
Great job, Peter. You are 98 percent successful.
- 百分之九十八 - 好耶 蜘蛛侠
- Ninety-eight? - Yeah, Spider-Man!
不 不 不
No, no, no.
怎么回事
What the hell?
嗨 蜘蛛侠
Hi, Spider-Man.
这就是你的乐队练习 是吧
Band practice, was it?
好耶 钢铁侠
Yeah, Iron Man!
斯塔克先生
Mr. Stark.
嘿 斯塔克先生 我能做什么吗 你想要我做什么
Hey, Mr. Stark, could I do anything? What do you want me to do?
我觉得你做得够多了
I think you've done enough.
所以就这样了 你打算就这么逃跑
So that's it. You're just gonna run?
联邦调查局在那里守株待兔
Feds were waiting for us.
现在我们都在钢铁侠的雷达上了
Now we're on Iron Man's radar?
没错 我要逃跑了
Yeah, I'm running.
你也该逃跑
You should too.
你知道我不能那么做
You know I can't do that.
那你现在打算怎么办
So now what?
梅森 你能造那个高海拔真空密封器 让它按时运转吗
Mason, can you get that high-altitude seal thing up and running in time?
你说真的
Seriously?
好的 你不会后悔的
Yes. You will not regret this.
你加入吗
You in?
上回你闯了祸时
Previously on Peter Screws the Pooch...
我就告诉你别再这么做了
I tell you to stay away from this.
你反而黑了一件价值数百万美元的装备
Instead, you hacked a multimillion-dollar suit...
这样你就能背着我
so you could sneak around behind my back...
去做唯一那件我告诉你不要做的事
doing the one thing I told you not to do.
大家都没事吧
Is everyone okay?
这也不是你的功劳
No thanks to you.
不是我的功劳
No thanks to me?
有人在销售那些危险武器 我试着告诉你这件事
Those weapons were out there, and I tried to tell you about it...
但你不听
but you didn't listen.
要是你当初听了我的话 这些事就不会发生了
None of this would've happened if you had just listened to me.
要是你哪怕有一点点关心 你就会亲自到这里来
If you even cared, you'd actually be here.
我当然听了 孩子 你以为联邦调查局是谁叫来的
I did listen, kid. Who do you think called the FBI, huh?
你知不知道我是唯一一个信任你的人
Do you know I was the only one who believed in you?
其他所有人都觉得我是疯了 才会招收一个14岁的小孩
Everyone else said I was crazy to recruit a 14-year-old kid.
- 我15岁了 - 你这时闭嘴就好 明白吗
- I'm 15. - No, this is where you zip it, all right?
大人在说话 小孩别插嘴 要是今晚有人死掉怎么办
The adult is talking. What if somebody had died tonight?
一切就不同了 不是吗 因为那会是你的错
Different story, right? Because that's on you.
而要是你死了
And if you died...
我会觉得那是我的错
I feel like that's on me.
- 我不需要背上这种良心债 - 是的 先生
- I don't need that on my conscience. - Yes, sir.
- 我很抱歉 我明白 - 道歉没用
- I'm sorry. I understand. - Sorry doesn't cut it.
我只是想像你一样
I just wanted to be like you.
而我想要你比我更好
And I wanted you to be better.
这行不通 我要收回这身装备
It's not working out. I'm gonna need the suit back.
- 什么时候再给我 - 永远不给
- For how long? - Forever.
- 就是这样 - 不 不要 求你
- Yeah, that's how it works. - No, no. Please.
- 把它给我 - 求你 我只有这个了
- Let's have it. - Please, this is all I have.
没有这身装备 我什么也不是
I'm nothing without this suit.
如果没了这身装备你什么也不是 那你就不该拥有它
If you're nothing without this suit, then you shouldn't have it.
明白吗
Okay?
天啊 我听起来跟我爸一样
God, I sound like my dad.
我没带其他衣服
I don't have any other clothes.
好吧 我们会解决这个问题的
Okay, we'll sort that out.
嗨
Hey.
我这一整天一直给你打电话 但你就是不接
I've been calling you all day. You didn't answer your phone.
你不能这么做
You can't do that.
然后发生了这个渡轮事故
Then this ferry thing happens.
我给五个警察局打了电话
I've called five police stations.
五个警察局
Five.
我给你的五个朋友打了电话 也给奈德的妈妈打了电话
I called five of your friends. I called Ned's mother.
我没事 梅婶 我很好 真的 放松点 我没事
I'm fine. May, I'm okay. Honestly, just relax. I'm fine.
少说废话
Cut the bullshit.
我知道你被留堂了
I know you left detention.
我知道在华盛顿时你离开了酒店房间
I know you left the hotel room in Washington.
我知道你每晚都从家里偷溜出去
I know you sneak out of this house every night.
这不是没事
That's not fine.
彼得 你必须告诉我发生了什么事 告诉我吧
Peter, you have to tell me what's going on. Just lay it out.
这里只有我和你
It's just me and you.
我失去了去斯塔克公司实习的机会
I lost the Stark internship.
- 什么 - 是的
- What? - Yeah.
发生了什么事
What happened?
我以为我能很努力 而他会... 他会愿意... 你懂的
I just thought that I could work really hard and he could... He would... You know.
但我搞砸了
But I screwed it up.
没事的
It's okay, it's okay.
没关系的
It's okay.
我很抱歉我让你担心了
I'm sorry I made you worry.
我没想毁掉你的生活
I'm not trying to ruin your life.
嗯 我知道
Yeah, I know.
我只是...
Just...
- 我以前也从家里偷溜出去过 - 是啊
- I used to sneak out too. - Yeah.
去洗个澡 你身上臭死了
And take a shower. You smell.
臭得像从垃圾堆里钻出来似的
You smell like garbage.
我知道
I know.
彼得 你是个好孩子 也是个聪明的孩子
Peter, you're a good kid and you're a smart kid...
努力向前看 明白吗
so just try to keep your head straight, okay?
好的
Okay.
好了 出去吧
All right, get out of here.
你被开除了
Are you expelled?
你得去那个校长有十字弓的高中上学了
Do you have to go to that high school where the principal has a crossbow?
我很肯定这是个城市传说 还有 我没被开除
Pretty sure that's an urban myth, and, no, I'm not expelled.
你可真走运
You're so lucky.
答的不错 帕克先生
Muy bueno, se?or Parker.
嗨
Hey.
嘿
我以为你第五节课是微积分
I thought you had calculus fifth period.
我在做校友返校日的材料
Yeah, I was just doing some homecoming stuff.
嘿 听着 我...
Hey, look, I...
我想为比赛的事向你道歉
I just wanted to apologize about the whole decathlon thing.
没关系
It's fine.
上周 十项全能是最重要的事 但之后我差点死了
Last week, decathlon was the most important thing, but then I almost died.
不 我...
No, I'm...
我是说...
I just mean that...
我做得不对 尤其是...
it was not cool, especially...
因为...
because...
我喜欢你
I like you.
我知道
I know.
你知道
You do?
你根本藏不住秘密
You're terrible at keeping secrets.
那你绝对会大吃一惊的
Yeah, you'd be surprised.
我得去上课了 但...
I got to get to class, but...
我本想说我们该一起出去玩 但我会被...
I'd say we should hang out, but I'm gonna be in detention...
永远留堂 但是...
forever, but...
我猜你在返校日那天肯定已经有约了
I guess you already have a date to homecoming.
其实 我是忙着构思这个活动 还没时间去找伴儿 所以...
Actually, I was so busy planning it, I never really got around to that part, so...
那你愿意
Do you want to...
和我一起参加吗
go with me?
好啊 我很乐意
Yeah. Sure.
真的 我是说 棒极了 好啊
Really? I mean, great. Cool.
好啊
Cool.
其实我要走这边
I'm actually going that way.
梅婶婶 我需要你的帮助
May, I need your help.
穿过去或绕一圈
Through or around?
好了
Right?
今天要约会了 你有什么计划
It's game day. So, what's the plan?
给她开门
Open the door for her.
告诉她她看起来很美 但不能过分恭维 因为这会很瘆人
Tell her she looks nice, but not too much because that's creepy.
- 不能让人觉得你瘆得慌 - 是的
- Don't be creepy. - No.
和她跳舞时 我要把手放在她的胯部
When I dance with her, I'm putting my hands on her hips.
没问题
I got this.
- 我爱你 - 再见
- Love you. - Bye.
你肯定就是彼得
You must be Peter.
没错
Yeah.
我是莉兹的爸爸
I'm Liz's dad.
握个手吧
Put her there.
挺有劲啊
Hell of a grip.
进来吧 来吧
Come on in here. Come on.
嗨 彼得
Hi, Peter.
你看起来真帅
You look very handsome.
谢谢
Thank you.
你叫对他的名字了
You got his name right?
- 弗雷迪 - 是彼得
- Freddie? - Peter.
彼得 彼得
Peter. Peter.
我去叫莉兹
I'm gonna go get Liz.
好的
Okay.
你还好吧 彼得
You all right, Pete?
挺好的
Yeah.
你的脸色看起来很苍白
Because you look pale.
你想喝些什么吗
You want something to drink?
波旁酒 苏格兰威士忌 还是其他什么
A bourbon or a Scotch, or something like that?
我还没到可以喝酒的年纪
I'm not old enough to drink.
回答正确
That's the right answer.
- 你看起来真美 - 你夸得我都不好意思了 爸爸
- Do you look beautiful. - Please don't embarrass me, Dad.
她很美 不是吗 彼得
Doesn't she, Pete?
没错 你看起来真的很美
Yeah, you look really good.
再次回答正确
Once again, that's the right answer.
这是胸花吗
Is that a corsage?
谢了
Thanks.
嘿 我是你们的司机 准备出发吧
Well, hey, I'm your chauffeur, so let's get this show on the road.
还不行 我得照几张照片 宝贝 好了
No, no, no, we have to take some pictures, babe. All right.
- 看这里 真棒 - 妈妈
- Oh, right here. Perfect. - Mom.
好了 你们俩站好了
Okay. Come on, you guys.
彼得 靠近点
Peter, closer.
笑一个
Smile.
好了
There you go.
- 先生 你不必开车送我们 - 不 这没什么大不了
- Sir, you don't have to drive us. - No, no, it's not a big deal.
我正好要出城 只是顺路送送你们
I'm going out of town. It's right on my way.
- 他总是往外跑 玩得开心点 - 这是最后一次
- He's always going. Have fun. - Last time.
- 谢谢 - 我发誓
- Thank you. - Promise.
他真可爱
He's cute.
- 几天后见 好了 - 再见 宝贝
- See you in a couple of days. All right. - Bye, baby.
走了 佩德罗
Come on, Pedro.
- 再见 彼得 玩得开心点 - 嗯 我会的
- Bye, Peter. Have fun. - Yeah, I will.
- 你打算做什么 彼得 - 什么
- What are you gonna do, Pete? - What?
毕业后你想做什么工作
When you graduate, what do you think you'll do?
- 我不知道 - 别盘问他了 爸爸
- Oh, I don't know. - Don't grill him, Dad.
只是单纯聊聊
Just saying, you know.
你们这些上这个高中的孩子们
All you guys who go to that school...
不都是早早把人生规划好了 不是吗
you pretty much have your life planned out, right?
没有 我才上高二
Yeah, no, I'm just a sophomore.
彼得是托尼·斯塔克手下的实习生 我觉得他不必担心工作的事
Peter has an internship with Tony Stark. I think he doesn't have to worry.
真的 是那个斯塔克
Really? Stark?
很厉害的
So cool.
你在他那里做什么工作
What do you do?
其实 我不再是他手下的实习生了
Yeah, actually, I don't intern for him anymore.
- 真的 - 是的 那工作变得...
- Seriously? - Yeah, it got...
很无聊
boring.
那工作很无聊 你可是能和蜘蛛侠一起四处闲逛
It was boring? You got to hang out with Spider-Man.
真的 和蜘蛛侠
Really? Spider-Man?
他是什么样的人
What's he like?
他人很好
Yeah, he's nice.
是个很好的人
Nice man.
很可靠的家伙
Solid dude.
看啊 真可爱
Look. So cute.
我见过你 对吧 我是说...
I've seen you around, right? I mean...
在某个地方 我们有没有... 你的声音...
somewhere. We've... Have we ever...? Because even the voice...
他和我一起参加了学术十项全能比赛
He does Academic Decathlon with me.
也参加了我的派对
And he was at my party.
那是个很棒的派对 非常棒
It was a great party, really great, yeah.
- 漂亮的房子 很多窗户 - 你只在那里呆了两秒钟
- Beautiful house, a lot of windows. - You were there for, like, two seconds.
那是... 我呆的时间超过两秒钟
That was... I was there longer than two seconds.
- 你突然消失了 - 不 我没有消失
- You disappeared. - No. No, I did not disappear.
不 你消失了 像你经常做的那样 消失了 就像在华盛顿那时一样
Yes, you did. You disappeared like you always do, like you did in D.C. too.
在华盛顿发生的事可真糟糕
That's terrible what happened down there in D.C. though.
你当时害怕吗
Were you scared?
我肯定在你的老朋友蜘蛛侠
I'll bet you were glad when your old pal Spider-Man...
出现在那台电梯里时你很高兴 对吗
showed up in the elevator though, huh?
是的 其实我并没有上去
Yeah, well, I actually didn't go up.
我在楼下目睹了那一切
I saw it all from the ground.
没错
Yeah.
他那天在那里真是件幸事
Very lucky that he was there that day.
蜘蛛侠真是了不起
Good old Spider-Man.
爸爸 绿灯亮了
Dad, the light.
我们到了 你们该下车了
Here we are. End of the line.
谢谢 爸爸
Thanks, Dad.
你先进去吧 甜心
You head in there, gumdrop.
身为爸爸的我要和彼得聊一聊
I'm gonna give Peter the "dad" talk.
别被他吓到了
Don't let him intimidate you.
我爱你
Love you.
- 我也爱你 甜心 - 一路平安
- Love you, gumdrop. - Have a safe flight.
嗨
Hi.
你们打扮得真好看
You guys look so pretty.
她知道吗
Does she know?
知道什么
Know what?
所以就是不知道了 很好
So she doesn't. Good.
做事小心谨慎
Close to the vest.
我喜欢这点
I admire that.
我自己有几个小秘密
I've got a few secrets of my own.
我不想我女儿和别人交往的一切理由
Of all the reasons I didn't want my daughter to date....
彼得
Peter...
没有什么比家人更重要
nothing is more important than family.
你救了我女儿的命
You saved my daughter's life.
我永远不会忘记你的恩情
I could never forget something like that.
所以我会给你一个机会
So I'm gonna give you one chance.
你准备好了吗
Are you ready?
你走出门 忘记发生的一切
You walk through those doors, you forget any of this happened...
还有永远不许
and don't you ever, ever...
再干扰我的生意
interfere with my business again.
因为如果你敢再这么做
Because if you do...
我会杀了你
I'll kill you...
和所有你爱的人
and everybody you love.
我会杀死你
I'll kill you dead.
我会这么做来保护我的家人 你明白吗
That's what I'll do to protect my family. Do you understand?
嗨
Hey.
我刚饶了你一命 现在你该说什么
I just saved your life. Now what do you say?
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
你现在进去参加派对 让我女儿玩得开心点 明白吗
Now you go on in there and you show my daughter a good time, okay?
但别开心过了头
Just not too good.
嗨
Hey.
他对你说了什么
What did he say to you?
我得走了
Gotta go.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你不该得到这种对待
You don't deserve this.
他给了你选择
He gave you a choice.
- 你选了错的路 - 搞什么
- You chose wrong. - What the hell?
这个蹩脚的装扮是怎么回事
What's with the crappy costume?
我的蛛网发射器
My web-shooters.
我一开始也不确定这玩意好不好用 不过我可真是惊喜
I wasn't sure about this thing at first, but damn.
受不了
Gross.
他为什么派你过来这里
Why did he send you here?
我猜你要带着这个疑问下地狱了
Guess you'll never know.
好准
Nice shot!
太棒了
Yes!
奈德 那个穿飞行服的家伙是莉兹的爸爸
Ned, the guy with the wings is Liz's dad.
- 什么 - 我得告诉斯塔克先生
- What? - I know. I gotta tell Mr. Stark.
打电话给哈皮·霍根 他是斯塔克先生的保安队长
Call Happy Hogan. He's Mr. Stark's head of security.
找台电脑 追踪我的手机
Get a computer and track my phone.
你不会有事吧
Will you be okay?
快点 我们得在他离开市里之前抓住他
Hurry, we gotta catch him before he leaves town.
晚餐的事我很抱歉
I'm sorry about dinner...
但我尝得出来海鲈鱼新不新鲜 而刚才的那条可不新鲜 好吗 所以...
but I know when branzino's fresh, and that was not fresh, okay? So...
弗拉什 我需要你的车和手机
Flash, I need your car and phone.
先生 严格来说 这是我爸爸的车 所以我不能...
Sir, technically, this is my dad's car, sir. So I can't...
喂 奈德 嘿 你能听到我说话吗
Hello, Ned? Hey, hey, can you hear me?
我听着呢
Go for Ned.
奈德 我需要你追踪我手机的位置
Ned, I need you to track my phone for me.
好 可它在哪
Yeah, but where is it?
这招可真天才 好吧 他刚经过杰克逊大街的游戏驿站
Genius move. Okay, he just passed the GameStop on Jackson Avenue.
嘿 车头灯的开关在哪 我现在正开着弗拉什的车
Hey, where are the headlights on this thing? I'm in Flash's car.
- 我看下说明 - 好吧 我打开免提了
- I'll pull the specs. - Okay, you're on speakerphone.
- 你抢了弗拉什的车 太棒了 - 是啊 这感觉很棒
- You stole Flash's car. Awesome. - Yeah, it's awesome.
让开 把路让开 快让开
Get out of the way, get out of the way! Move!
- 你没事吧 - 我以前从没开过车
- Are you okay? - I've never driven before...
只和梅婶婶在停车场开过车 这简直是大跨步
only with May in parking lots. This is a huge step up.
嘿 你联系上哈皮了吗
Hey, have you gotten through to Happy yet?
嗯 我正联系着呢 我刚刚黑进了电话系统
Yeah. I'm working on it. I just gotta backdoor the phone system.
我是技术特工了
Guy in the chair.
九分钟后起飞
Takeoff in nine minutes.
喂 喂 你是谁
Hello? Hello? Who is this?
- 哈皮先生 我是奈德 - 谁
- Mr. Happy, it's Ned. - Who?
我是彼得·帕克的伙伴 我有件十万火急的事要告诉你
I'm an associate of Peter Parker. Got something very important to tell you...
你是在逗我吧
You gotta be shitting me.
该死
Damn.
嘿 奈德 车头灯要怎么开
Hey, Ned, how we coming on with those headlights?
方向盘左边的圆形按钮 顺时针转一下
Round knob to the left of the steering wheel, turn clockwise.
方向盘左边 好的
Left, okay.
好了 车头灯打开了 我的手机现在在哪
Okay, perfect. So where's my phone now?
他停在了布鲁克林的一个老工业园里
He stopped in an old industrial park in Brooklyn.
什么 这说不通 他说他要出城的
What? That makes no sense. He said he was going out of town.
真奇怪 我联系上了哈皮先生 顺便一提 我觉得他不喜欢你
Weird. Oh, I reached Mr. Happy. Don't think he likes you, by the way.
听起来像是他在赶飞机
It sounded like he was catching a flight.
他说有什么东西要在九分钟后起飞
He said something about taking off in nine minutes.
- 什么 - 他周围全是箱子
- What? - He was surrounded by boxes.
箱子 今天是搬迁日
Boxes? It's moving day.
今天是搬迁日 他打算抢劫那架飞机
It's moving day. He's gonna rob that plane.
我必须阻止他
I gotta stop him!
好了 八分钟后收起起落架
All right, wheels up in eight minutes.
我们得装上托尼的反浩克旧战甲
We just got to load Tony's old Hulkbuster Armor...
美队新盾牌的原型和梅金
prototype for Cap's new shield, and the Meging...
梅...梅什么...
The Meg... The...
雷神的神奇腰带
Thor's magic belt.
好了 减速 你快到了 那个工业园就在你的右边
Okay, slow down. You're getting close. It's on your right.
- 什么 - 往右转
- What? - Turn right.
- 彼得 你没事吧 - 我没事
- Peter. Are you okay? - Yeah.
继续想办法联系哈皮
Just keep trying to get through to Happy.
这是我的荣幸 蜘蛛侠
It's been an honor, Spider-Man.
你在这干嘛 怎么不去参加舞会
What are you doing here? There's a dance.
我...
I'm...
在看...
looking...
小黄片
at porn.
嗨
Hey!
惊讶吗
Surprised?
嘿 彼得
Oh, hey, Pete.
我没听到你进来
I didn't hear you come in.
一切都结束了 我抓到你了
It's over. I've got you.
我得告诉你 彼得
You know, I gotta tell you, Pete...
我真的很欣赏你的勇气
I really, really admire your grit.
我明白莉兹为什么喜欢你了
I see why Liz likes you.
真的 但你第一次来到我家时
I do. When you first came to the house...
我不确定 想着"莉兹竟然喜欢这小子" 但我现在明白了
I wasn't sure. I thought, "Really?" But I get it now.
你怎么能这么对她
How could you do this to her?
这么对她 我没对她做任何事 彼得
To her? I'm not doing anything to her, Pete.
我是为了她才这么做的
I'm doing this for her.
没错
Yeah.
彼得
Peter...
你还年轻
you're young.
你不明白这个世界的运转规则
You don't understand how the world works.
但我明白卖武器给罪犯是不对的
But I understand that selling weapons to criminals is wrong.
那你觉得你的好朋友斯塔克建起那座大厦的钱是哪来的呢
How do you think your buddy Stark paid for that tower?
还有他那些小玩具
Or any of his little toys?
那些人 彼得 上面那些人
Those people, Pete, those people up there...
他们有钱有势 可以为所欲为
the rich and the powerful, they do whatever they want.
像我们这样的人
Guys like us...
像你我这样的人
like you and me...
他们根本不在乎
they don't care about us.
我们给他们修路搭桥 为他们做一切斗争
We build their roads, and we fight all their wars...
做一切事 但他们根本不在乎我们
and everything, but they don't care about us.
我们得挑他们剩下的 得吃他们剩下的
We have to pick up after them. We have to eat their table scraps.
世界上的规则就是这样
That's how it is.
我知道你明白我在说什么 彼得
I know you know what I'm talking about, Peter.
你为什么要告诉我这些
Why are you telling me this?
因为我想要你理解我
Because I want you to understand.
而且...
And...
我需要一点时间启动飞行服
I needed a little time to get her airborne.
抱歉 彼得
I'm sorry, Peter.
你在说什么 那玩意还没碰着我呢
What are you talking about? That thing hasn't even touched me yet.
没错 不过...
True. Then again...
我也没想让它碰到你
wasn't really trying to.
头儿 他们正在给发动机充电
Chief, they're powering up engines.
- 好 我知道了 - 快点过来
- Okay. Yeah, yeah. - Come on, come on, come on.
好了 准备好了
Okay, ready?
有人吗
Hello?
来人啊
Hello!
拜托 来个人
Please, hey.
拜托 来人帮帮忙 我在下面这里
Hey, please. I'm down here.
我在下面这里 我被困住了
I'm down here. I'm stuck.
我被困住了 我动不了 我不能...
I'm stuck. I can't move. I can't...
如果没了这身装备你什么也不是 那你就不该拥有它
If you're nothing without this suit, then you shouldn't have it.
加油 彼得
Come on, Peter.
加油 蜘蛛侠
Come on, Spider-Man.
Come on, Spider-Man!
准备拦截 绿灯 放行
Launch for intercept. Green light. Green light.
哦耶
Oh, yeah.
启动反光面板
Retroreflective panels engaged.
看到那架飞机了 但我感到了一点小小的阻力
Got a visual on the plane, but I'm feeling a little resistance.
大概只是新涡轮带来的阻力
It's probably just drag on the new turbines.
小心隐形摄像机 呆在盲点区域
Look out for the cloaking cameras. Stay in the blind spots.
天啊 我的天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
部署高海拔真空密封器
Deploying high-altitude vacuum seal.
这最好能起作用 梅森
This better work, Mason.
相信我 头儿 哪怕拿到一个箱子 我们这辈子都不用愁了
Trust me, boss, even one of those boxes and we are set for life.
没错
Yeah.
你有三十秒时间进入驾驶舱
You have 30 seconds to get to the cockpit...
更改他们的安保系统
and override their security.
克隆异频雷达收发器信号
Cloning transponder signal.
发射傀儡无人机
Launching decoy drone.
输入新坐标点
Entering new coordinates.
很好 现在飞机已经出发了
Good, so it's on its way.
- 没错 先生 飞机航线正确 - 好的 谢谢
- Yes, sir, right on course. - Okay, thank you.
没问题
All right.
太棒了
Hot dog.
这只是个典型的校友返校日
Just a typical homecoming...
在一个隐形飞机的外面
on the outside of an invisible jet...
和我女朋友的爸爸战斗
fighting my girlfriend's dad.
老天啊
Oh, God!
我真不敢相信这竟然成功了
I can't believe that worked.
头儿 飞机高度正在降低 快点离开那里
Chief, they're losing altitude. Get out of there.
我不会空着手回家
I'm not going home empty-handed.
我的天
Oh, my God.
快离开那里 你在干嘛
Get out of there. What are you doing?
拜托转弯 求你转弯吧
Please turn, please turn!
嘿 佩德罗
Hey, Pedro.
我赢了
Bingo.
你的飞行服
Your wingsuit.
你的飞行服要爆炸了
Your wingsuit's going to explode!
该回家了 彼得
Time to go home, Pete.
我是在救你的命
I'm trying to save you!
不
No.
这看起来太不可思议了 这一整件...
It looked so insane. That whole...
感觉太不可思议了
Like, it was just crazy.
他...他就像...
He... He was just, like....
而你就像...
And you were like....
然后我击中了他 用那个...
And then I just hit him with the....
这太... 我的天啊
It was so... Oh, my God.
我是说 你救了我
I mean, you saved me.
这太棒了
It was awesome.
嘿 莉兹
Hey, Liz.
我会想你的
I'm gonna miss you.
拜
Bye.
莉兹
Liz.
莉兹 听着 我很抱歉
Liz, look, I'm so sorry.
你道过很多次歉了 这回是为什么道歉
You say that a lot. What are you sorry for this time?
这次舞会的事
The dance?
这么做可真没品
That was a pretty crappy thing to do.
是啊 但我...
Well, yeah, but I...
我是说 你爸爸的事... 我无法想象你现在的感受
I mean, your dad... I can't imagine what you're going through.
要是有什么我能帮忙的地方...
If there's anything I can do to help....
我想我们要搬到俄勒冈州去
I guess we're moving to Oregon.
妈妈说那里很好 所以我没事
Mom says it's nice there, so that's cool.
反正审判期间 爸爸不想让我们呆在这里 所以...
Anyways, Dad doesn't want us here during the trial. So....
莉兹 我...
Liz, I... I...
再见 彼得
Bye, Peter.
无论你身上发生了什么事 我希望你能搞定它
Whatever's going on with you, I hope you figure it out.
祝贺你们拿到了十项全能全国冠军
Congratulations, decathlon national champions.
好耶
Yeah!
我得马上把这个放回奖杯陈列柜里
I'll have to put this back in the trophy case soon...
但按照惯例现在拿出来给大家看一下是 激励大家再接再厉
but just for motivation right now at this practice.
我现在是身具优势 但明年我们将需要一个新队长
I'm ahead of the game, but we will need a new team captain next year.
我要任命米歇尔为新队长
So I am appointing Michelle.
好耶
Yeah!
谢谢
Thank you.
我...我朋友都叫我MJ
My... My friends call me MJ.
我以为你没有朋友
I thought you didn't have any friends.
我是没有
I didn't.
- 我先走了 - 嘿 你要去哪
- I gotta go. - Hey, where you going?
你在隐藏什么 彼得
What are you hiding, Peter?
我只是在开玩笑 我才不在乎呢 再见
I'm just kidding. I don't care. Bye.
- 好了 我们该练习一下 - 没错
- All right, so we should run some drills. - Yeah.
嘿 哈皮 你怎么... 你来这干嘛
Hey, Happy. What...? What are you doing here?
我欠你的
I really owe you one.
我不知道没了这份工作我该怎么办
I don't know what I would do without this job.
我是在 在我遇到托尼之前...
I mean, before I met Tony...
你在这呆了多久了
So how long you been here?
久到让人尴尬的地步 老板想见你
Long enough to be awkward. Boss wants to see you.
- 他也来了 - 在蹲马桶吗 不 他在北部
- Is he here too? - In the toilet? No, he's upstate.
北部 你是说 那个北部吗
Upstate... Like, upstate-upstate?
是的 我们走吧
Yeah, let's go.
瞧瞧
Take a look.
相当不错 不是吗
It's pretty impressive, huh?
他们刚刚改建完整个建筑
They just finished remodeling the whole thing.
- 这可不是天天都能看到的 - 你们到了啊
- You don't see that every day. - Oh, there they are.
来的路上顺利吗
How was the ride up?
- 很好 - 让我和这孩子单独聊两分钟
- Good. - Give me a minute with the kid.
- 真的吗 - 真的
- Seriously? - Yeah.
我得和这孩子谈谈
I gotta talk to the kid.
我会紧跟在后面
I'll be close behind.
跟远一点怎么样 好吗 保持距离也是件好事
How about a loose follow? All right? Boundaries are good.
抱歉我拿走了你的装备
Sorry I took your suit.
你早猜到了吧 其实 事实证明
You had it coming. Actually, it turns out it was...
那正是你所需要的严爱时刻
the perfect tough-love moment that you needed.
为了督促你前进 不是吗 你不这么想 你不这么认为
To urge you on, right? Wouldn't you think? Don't you think?
- 我猜是吧 - 说是就行了
- I guess. - Let's just say it was.
- 斯塔克先生 我真的... - 你犯过大错 很严重的大错
- Mr. Stark, I really... - You screwed the pooch hard, bigtime.
但之后你做了正确的事
But then you did the right thing.
带那只狗去了免费诊所 你养大了那只杂种狗...
Took the dog to the free clinic, you raised the hybrid puppies....
好吧 我这类比用得不算最好
All right, not my best analogy.
我误解了你
I was wrong about you.
我觉得 只要稍加指导
I think, with a little more mentoring...
你会真正融入这支队伍
you could be a real asset to the team.
- 融入...这支队伍 - 是啊 总而言之...
- To the...? To the team? - Yeah. Anyway...
那扇门后有大约五十名记者 真正的记者 不是博主
there's about 50 reporters behind that door. Real ones, not bloggers.
如果你准备好了
When you're ready...
何不试试这身装备
why don't you try that on?
我将向全世界隆重介绍 复仇者联盟最新正式成员
And I'll introduce the world to the newest official member of the Avengers:
蜘蛛侠
Spider-Man.
我...
I....
好好看看
Yeah, give that a look.
新闻发布会之后 哈皮会带你去看你的房间
After the press conference, Happy will show you to your room...
也就是你的新住处
your new quarters.
他的房间在哪里 挨着幻视
Where's he between? He's next to Vision?
- 是的 幻视不喜欢门 - 这可真有趣
- Yeah, Vision's not big on doors. - It's fun.
他也不喜欢墙
Or walls.
你会适应这里的
You'll fit right in.
谢谢你 斯塔克先生
Thank you, Mr. Stark.
但我还是不加入你们了
But I'm good.
你不加入了 你怎么能不加入呢
You're good? Good...? How are you good?
我是说 我更愿意多当一段时间平凡人
Well, I mean, I'd rather just stay on the ground for a little while.
当个好邻居蜘蛛侠
Friendly neighborhood Spider-Man.
总得有人保护弱者 不是吗
Somebody's got to look out for the little guy, right?
你这是在拒绝我
You're turning me down?
你最好好好考虑一下 看看那个
You better think about this. Look at that.
看看我
Look at me.
这是你最后的机会 同意还是拒绝
Last chance. Yes or no?
- 我拒绝 - 好吧
- No. - Okay.
这有点斯普林斯汀的工人阶级英雄范儿 我还是蛮欣赏的
It's kind of a Springsteen-y, working-class hero vibe that I dig.
哈皮会送你回家
Happy will take you home.
- 好吗 - 好的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
介意先去车里等一会吗 我等会就过去
Mind waiting in the car? I need a minute.
- 谢谢你 斯塔克先生 - 不客气 帕克先生
- Thank you, Mr. Stark. - Yes, Mr. Parker, very well.
- 回头见 - 好的
- See you around. - Okay.
这是个考验 对吗
That was a test, right?
- 那后面没人 对吧 - 是的 你通过了
- There's nobody back there? - Yes, you passed.
- 好了 赶紧溜吧 小伙子 - 谢谢 斯塔克先生
- All right, skedaddle there, young buck. - Thank you, Mr. Stark.
嗯 也谢谢你
Yeah, thank you.
我跟你说过他是个好孩子
Told you he's a good kid.
- 那个孩子呢 - 他走了
- Where's the kid? - He left.
- 大家都在等着呢 - 他其实做了个成熟的选择
- Everybody's waiting. - He actually made a mature choice.
- 这把我们都惊呆了 - 你把这事搞砸了
- It just surprised the heck out of us. - Did you screw this up?
- 是他告诉那孩子去车里等的 - 你在逗我吗
- He told the kid to go wait in the car. - Are you kidding?
我这里有一屋子的人等着
I have a room full of people in there waiting...
一个爆炸性的公告 我该告诉他们什么
for some big announcement. What will I tell them?
瞎编点什么 不如...
Think of something. How about...?
- 哈皮 你还带着那个戒指吗 - 我...
- Hap, you still got that ring? - Do I...? I...?
- 那个订婚戒指 - 你是在逗我吗
- The engagement ring. - Are you kidding?
我自2008年起就一直随身带着它
I've been carrying this since 2008.
好的
Okay.
我想我能想个比这更好的办法
I think I can think of something better than that.
这会给我们争取些时间
Well, it would buy us a little time.
其实我们不太赶时间
Like we need time.
我真不敢相信你把这个装在口袋里
I can't believe you have that in your pocket.
- 要我给你开门吗 亲爱的 - 我自己来就好
- Want me to get the door for you, hon? - I got it.
梅婶 晚饭好了吗
Aunt May, did you do dinner already?
梅婶
May?
这什么鬼...
What the...?!
瞧瞧谁来了
Look who it is.
你和我最终来到同一个"夏令营"的几率有多大
What are the odds you and I'd end up at the same summer camp?
放轻松
Relax.
这个 这不怪你
This? It's not on you.
这要怪我们那个小蜘蛛朋友
It's on our little spider friend.
我外面有些哥们想见见他
I've got some boys on the outside who would love to meet him.
照个相 割断他的喉咙 把他的脑袋放进烘干机里
You know, take a picture, slice his throat, put his head in a dryer.
我听到些传闻
And I heard a rumor.
你知道他是谁
You know who he is.
如果我知道他是谁
If I knew who he was...
那他早就死了
he'd already be dead.
图姆斯 你的家人来探监了
Toomes, your family's here!
嘿 我是美国队长 在此跟你们说说
Hi, I'm Captain America, here to talk to you...
一个士兵或学生最宝贵的品质之一
about one of the most valuable traits a soldier or student can have.
就是耐心
Patience.
有时耐心是成功的关键
Sometimes patience is the key to victory.
有时耐心会带来不理想的结果
Sometimes it leads to very little...
让它看起来很划不来
and it seems like it's not worth it.
你会怀疑
And you wonder...
为何等待了这么久 却只等到了令人如此失望的结果
why you waited so long for something so disappointing.
这种视频我还要录多少
How many more of these?